{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f641cfba6a7877c0203"},"product_asin":"B09SGMJD2P","QAs":[{"question":"installation wale Deewar pe hol karke freme lagate hai","answer":"They did a very bad job in installing","votes":"0","username":"Rina","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does remote have display?","answer":"Nope very basic","votes":"0","username":"Rina","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"फैन ac है या dc","answer":"AC","votes":"0","username":"tushar","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Colour ‎white with silver deco strip and gold strip any difference???","answer":"Not any difference for me atleast… because i think ac’s cooling and performance matter","votes":"0","username":"Amit Rajawat","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much to should be paid to fill the remaining Window space?","answer":"At least 100","votes":"0","username":"Rina","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the Stabilizer installation charges extra?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rina","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac stand will came with this product??","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"how much unit cunsum per day 24 temp??","answer":"LLYOD 1 Ton AC consumes 1 unit of electricity per hour","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time do you take to install after delivery","answer":"With in 2 hours from the time of placing call for installation , the AC was installed .","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time do you take to install ac after delivery","answer":"You’ve to register and call Llyod they usually send someone in 2 days","votes":"0","username":"Mitali kukreja","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Room size 12 x 10 feet which size will be purchase?","answer":"1ton AC is sufficient for this room size","votes":"0","username":"Ritu khasa","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much electricity load is required? I have only 2KW can it work?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya yeh Window AC hot and cold hai","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchenge offer","answer":"I got very good exchange offer with this ac","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges for window 1 ton AC","answer":"There is installation charges it's optional","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does company provide installation or we have to arrange it ourself?","answer":"Company provide installation with charges","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Length of wire with the unit?","answer":"It's around 1.5m approximately","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if i do not want installation","answer":"It affects your warranty","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Installation free for this AC?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to do installation?","answer":"With some mechanics","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it fit in window having 22 inch width ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about it's installation","answer":"Not free","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation of havells lloyd ac is free?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Chandra","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any charges for installation?","answer":"Yes , very heavy charges for installation. The company charged me Rs 800/- in cash ,  No receipt was given","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is remote digital?","answer":"Remote is not digital.... but advertisement shows this as digital","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation included in this beacause nothing written about installation?","answer":"No installation","votes":"0","username":"Ritu khasa","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model year please","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Ritu khasa","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to arrange installation?","answer":"Just give a phone call to LLYOD call center","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about installation?","answer":"Installation of this window AC was done with in 30 minutes as it was just drilling 6 holes / fixing the outer  box &  just inserting the AC unit & plugging in the PIN for power","votes":"0","username":"Vijaykumar  Raverkar","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we get warranty card?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation free?","answer":"No, It is paid","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will amazon send someone for installation ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it the inverter AC","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation being offered?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I install this myself? Or I have to get itinstalled by lloyd technitian only?","answer":"Get it installed by Lloyd technician only","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav Chauhan","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require stabilizer? Or it can run without stabilizer?","answer":"It requires a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav Chauhan","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does stabilizer is require with this AC?","answer":"It requires a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav Chauhan","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Konse year ka make ya model hai?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Vaibhav Chauhan","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fan motor in copper or aluminium?","answer":"Copper","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we unbox itself or wait for an engg","answer":"It's better to wait for technician","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is actual dimension. The image shows width as 57 cm but specs field shows 60 cm.","answer":"60cm","votes":"0","username":"NILESH","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f651cfba6a7877c0210"},"product_asin":"B09TNKLD47","QAs":[{"question":"Is it convertable?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"varun","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Use alexa","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ashok","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it convertable?","answer":"Yes 4 ways swing","votes":"0","username":"ashok","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work over inverter and is there specific inverter model for this?","answer":"Don’t buy Lloyd you can go for OG","votes":"0","username":"rohit d.","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much warranty on pcb, compressor and all over warranty","answer":"One on pcb 10 on compressor. Lelo Bhai mast ac hai. I got it at 36k","votes":"0","username":"sagar","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i get the installation done from an outside vendor will the warranty get affected?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a mistake in Wattage Rating (5100 Watt) ??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a mistake in wattage rating (Wattage ‎5100 Watts) ??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have auto clean?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"exchange avalable","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor and indoor both are copper.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Parshant rana","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does lloyd provide amc","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warranty for PCB ?","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"satyanarayana","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want my bill and warranty card","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SUBRATA SAHA","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the range of power watt in Stabilizer?","answer":"you have received standard voltage (200v to 230v) Single Booster Stabilizer enough. If you received below 200v better to use Double booster Stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"MURUGAN VEERAMUTHU…","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maximum and minimum temperature ?","answer":"16","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it for both summers and winters","answer":"For summer yes. For winter, no. The Aux heat button is just for show.","votes":"0","username":"Suhas V. Sarkale","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this all weather?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"sagar","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a wifi model ot not","answer":"No. Only advertising WiFi model.","votes":"0","username":"Suhas V. Sarkale","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why GST is not correctly calculated, it's 28% but here charge 22% only","answer":"22","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the PCB warranty duration?","answer":"1 year ,i think","votes":"0","username":"ashok","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty???","answer":"1 year extrean warranty","votes":"0","username":"Ahamad basha","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i used 10 Hrs in a day so how much electricity bill in a month","answer":"Around 800-900","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot and cool hy ki nhi","answer":"Cooll","votes":"0","username":"Israfil Tarafder","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is valv cover is included with outdoor unit","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"You told one year and 10 years on compressor. how many  on PCB","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"TAPAS KUMAR PANDA","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f651cfba6a7877c021b"},"product_asin":"B09TNBCM4Q","QAs":[{"question":"Copper pipe is in the box only.some of them tell there is no copper pipes and no more doubt I have already Ac line is there any charges for fitting","answer":"Yes charge for fitting","votes":"0","username":"anil kumar pandey","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac kine watt da h","answer":"1.5 ton da but old model hai","votes":"0","username":"Beant Singh","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"alexa  (wifi)  connectivity available in 2022 model?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sunil","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product delivery not available at  pincode : 282005","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sunil","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges for ac","answer":"Power consumption takes high","votes":"0","username":"Snehitha","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper pipe is included in this model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model year","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much copper pipe come with the box","answer":"10 mt","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty period on pcb ???","answer":"1 Year","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is copper  condenser ?","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"Gourav","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Llyod invetor 1.5 Ac Year of manufacture is current or 2021","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Gourav","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they deliver both outer and indoor unit  together?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gourav","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need to buy seperate Wifi router for connectivity ?","answer":"If you have 2 mobile than you can easily connect your LLOYD AC wifi","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh chudasama","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compressor stand ayega sath me ?","answer":"Yes.  But u will be charged for it. Worth Rs1200. And 500 for fitting.","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac ka stand aaye ga sath ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper wire is missing in the box?  Which i ordered?","answer":"It comes with the box. Should be of 2mtrs","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fitting ka extra amount laga","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac delivery ke bad ghr pe kb lgegi","answer":"next day","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Work with Alexa??","answer":"I don't hv Alexa but it works with google-Home. It take voice commands on wi-fi on google-Hone app.","votes":"0","username":"Mahendra Rawat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lloyd pcb kitna warranty hai","answer":"1year, if purchased on-line and 5 years if purchased from Lloyd store.","votes":"0","username":"Mahendra Rawat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"PCB ka Kitni warranty hai","answer":"jo prodect ke sath hi","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of elaectric chord provided with the unit","answer":"It is copper wire and good strength for bearing requirements.","votes":"0","username":"Mahendra Rawat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i install my ac with another vendor","answer":"No, it may loose your warranty.","votes":"0","username":"Mahendra Rawat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac inverter ac with convertible capacity control?","answer":"It is inverter AC, not convertible.","votes":"0","username":"Mahendra Rawat","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper wires wil be given or not?","answer":"Yes , it will be in the box","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote is available or not","answer":"Yes available","votes":"0","username":"Parmar naresh…","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the comprehensive warranty and compressor warranty?","answer":"10 year","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much suitable for room sixe","answer":"10\\12 can be easily cooled.","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"With copper Pipe or not as many users deny that they don't get Pipe in box, plz cnfrm?","answer":"The pipe comes with the box. 2mtrs long,  and more than that is chargeable.","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i change temperature and swing thru alexa voice command?","answer":"Yes indeed. It is Wi-Fi connected.","votes":"0","username":"Prashant","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get all connecting copper pipes and brackets also with these?","answer":"I got everything. And working fine","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"It give pipe","answer":"Yes, 1.5 miter pipe","votes":"0","username":"Bala","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the meaning of Wi-Fi ac","answer":"Wi-Fi ac ka matalab hota hai ke apne mobile se control kar sakte ho Ac ka speed.","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there dust filter and auto sleep mode option  available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i open my self ac box","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"With fitting? No extra charge?","answer":"Yes ofcourse extra charge available and Traveling ka Bhi","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"can pcb warrenty extended ?","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"AKIL SHAMA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wara ty period of the unit","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"You dont provide brackets for outdoor unit","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ls18i35wshl may pcbkitna year warranty hai","answer":"1 year may be","votes":"0","username":"Raghav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f651cfba6a7877c0226"},"product_asin":"B09SGNCGFK","QAs":[{"question":"Does it comes with gas","answer":"Yes it comes as ready to use, only installation is required","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compreser warranty","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compreser warrant","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this invertor or non invertor ac","answer":"Invertor","votes":"0","username":"S","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free or not?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ashu nainwal","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get GST invoice","answer":"You can download invoice from the app itself, from order section, 'download invoice' option is there","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does its compressor start automatically?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a mistake in Wattage Rating (5000 Watt) ??","answer":"This is around 3600 watts","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need stabilizer","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Split ac our window ac","answer":"Split AC","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Split AC","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do it blow hot air also?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Current model and year ?","answer":"2020 model","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Current morel and year ?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model and year ?","answer":"2020 year & model is written at the top of the product","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter or non inverter AC","answer":"It is inverter AC but I was sent half part inverter and half non inverter and when the replacement was ordered no information was provided of delivery it was late by 5 days and then i had to cancel it","votes":"0","username":"Vaishali Tiwari","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Details about guarenty","answer":"1 year on entire product & 5 year on compressor","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model??","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use it in a sheet roof house ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ashu nainwal","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation is free","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ashu nainwal","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the copper pipe included in the package and is it 3 mts long?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ashu nainwal","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Under model it is mentioned 2021 model but at listing it says 2020 model ? Which one is correct ?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"ashu nainwal","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold","answer":"What kind of a question is that ? AC is for regulating Temperatures often by cooling.. If you need warming buy a room heater... I can't believe the question...","votes":"0","username":"CHANDAN HS","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does outer unit stand included?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Srivastav","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to turn on the horizontal swing ?","answer":"Manual","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Srivastav","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much copper pipe will it come with?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Srivastav","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the copper pipe included and wire","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Srivastav","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who do i contact for installation","answer":"Install LLOYD App then Scan the Scan code & register for installation","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Srivastav","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inverter or non inverter","answer":"Non inverter","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC hbe wifi?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ayan Chakraborty","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f651cfba6a7877c0231"},"product_asin":"B08X2Q1C58","QAs":[{"question":"Can we get only indoor unit for this modal","answer":"Absolutely NO","votes":"0","username":"AmazingStocks","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac has wifi remote feature","answer":"No WiFi,it’s WiFi ready for it you need to installed separate device","votes":"0","username":"hema kumar","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c0233"},"product_asin":"B09SGQB576","QAs":[{"question":"Is this hot and cold","answer":"No. Only cold","votes":"0","username":"Bhavyansh","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Energy consumptain 1hour","answer":"8 hours , 28 temperature, 2 point fan speed","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much should I have to pay for installation?","answer":"Rs900+GST=Rs1200/- They may ask more. Wall Bracket has to be purchased separately for Approximately 600-750Rs","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used for heating also in winter season","answer":"No it's not all weather AC","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Should we have to pay the installation charges?","answer":"Yes we have to pay","votes":"0","username":"Nagender Reddy","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer required?","answer":"If you have stable voltage in your home then it's not required. I have not installed the stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter one???","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"Nagender Reddy","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compresser  warranty","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 1 Ton or 1.5 Ton??.In title it is mentioned as 1.5ton but in comparison with other products it shows 1ton","answer":"It's 1 ton AC","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model 2020 or 2022 model","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dis is 3 star or 5 star?","answer":"3","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is indoor copper","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"PCB Warranty ?","answer":"1Year","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"This unit required stabilizer","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"This unit is required stabilize yes ot no","answer":"Stabilizer required","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is instollation free","answer":"No Need to Pay 990+GST=1200/-","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is inverter ac or fixed speed ac, at top pics showing as inverter & in features below mentioned as non-inverter???","answer":"Not fixed speed","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where to contact for installation post delivery?","answer":"May need to wait for 2-4days for installation","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter AC?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SURESH D","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any installation charges??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chanfu","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Condenser is copper?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"KRISHNA BHATT","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is 100 percent copper?","answer":"Yes 100 percent copper.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Out door unit Stand available?","answer":"Yes 100 percent copper.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Date of manufacture","answer":"2021 model","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any offers on credit card payment?","answer":"yes i got 1500 instant discount by using CITI Bank credit card.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stand /Bracket for outdoor fitting is available in the box","answer":"Yes all Items related to fitting in available in the box.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How did they calculate the annual energy consumption as 743 units? What wouuld be the  average  working hours hours on daily basis for this calculatio","answer":"I used this AC only at night ( around 8 hours)","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is price of this ac?","answer":"I buy it after discount 24800 rs.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the condensor pipes are of copper","answer":"Yes, condensor pieps are of copper.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the cost of 1.5 tonnes indoor unit  only of the split ac","answer":"I buy only 1 ton AC.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit is of copper or aluminum??","answer":"Outdoor unit is of fully copper.","votes":"0","username":"Rinku kumar","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c023e"},"product_asin":"B08V8FN59W","QAs":[{"question":"Weight kitna hi","answer":"वेट जानकर क्या करोगे,परफॉर्मेंस पूछो कैसा है,60किलो वजन ही है,अच्छी क्वालिटी है,ऑनलाइन एमोजोन से खरीदना कोई समस्या नहीं आयेगी,","votes":"0","username":"vishal kumar upadhyay","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c0240"},"product_asin":"B09SGN2N8P","QAs":[{"question":"Its written here stabilizer free function . In my region there is oft voltage fluctuations . Is it still safe to use it without stabilizer ?","answer":"This product comes with inbuilt stabilizer for its own parts to work smoothly. Required voltage 230 V and Current 15A. In case of areas where voltage fluctuates, it is advised to use a stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"why is installation pipe written in item list when supplier has removed it from the box? it costs around 3,000 rupees","answer":"If the items mentioned in the packing list doesn't match then give a complaint and ask for replacement. Although the pipe which comes with the product is very small and we have to buy it accordingly at an extra cost.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wifi connection ho","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have sbi debit card i want to purchase 1 ton ac with emi","answer":"Dont Purchase from Amazon, They are not sending Components For Installation. Big cheater Showing online but do not deliver nor proper response. I bought AC on 4th May but till Today could not get Installed","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model manufacturing year?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether Stabilizer is free for this product","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is capacity","answer":"I have 0.8T and 1.5T a/cs","votes":"0","username":"Shyam Kokku","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange option available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amit Roy","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"For2 nos, any extra offer? &installation charge?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amit Roy","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much units is the electric consumption if on an average using for 6hrs per day?","answer":"I am not sure as we don't use it everyday","votes":"0","username":"Shyam Kokku","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to install pcb chip and suggest the chip from where to buy please","answer":"Contact nearest supplier","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"No call from installation team even after 2nd day? What is the contact method?","answer":"I never experienced a problem with installation team.","votes":"0","username":"Shyam Kokku","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the installation kits provided exactly ? The description doesnot provide clarity.","answer":"Supplier Cheater. They have mentioned in Components llist Included in Online Showroom, but Upon Delivery they are saying that its not included. Do not Buy from Amazon. Else Do buy untill you are Embarrased. It may Happned with Anybody.","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Min temperature?","answer":"Min. Temp. of this product is 16 degrees","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the warranty of the pcb of lloyd inverter?","answer":"The manual and the customer care confirmed the PCB to be in warranty for limited 1 year.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the warranty of pcb","answer":"1 year as per the customer care","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wifi he kya","answer":"This particular AC doesn't have WIFI connectivity. Though other Lloyd AC has the feature","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wifi sistem","answer":"This particular AC doesn't have WIFI.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"swing option on or off available?","answer":"Generally all the AC's comes with Swing option. This one also has the feature.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"573201 delivery available","answer":"Contact customer care or check on their website. There is a place to check on their website only.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gurrenty or warrenty who gave customar","answer":"There 8s a limited warranty of 1 year in this AC. The warranty can be claimed by their Brand only.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no connecting pipe in the box, although its mentioned on the box","answer":"The connecting pipe which comes with this AC is small and it cannot be used in big areas. We need to buy the same and as per our requirements.","votes":"0","username":"Ramiz Islam","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it is inverter","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Kishor Kerai","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c024b"},"product_asin":"B09W3RF92L","QAs":[{"question":"fitting charges","answer":"I paid 500 Rs.","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"installation charges","answer":"I paid 500 Rs. But it is totally depend on the engineer how much they want to charge for window AC installation.","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"what are installation charges","answer":"On Lloyd website they haven’t mentioned charges for Window AC installation. As per the Lloyd customer care executive the AC installation engineer will call you and confirm you the price before coming.  The engineer came at my home charged INR 500/-","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation available with it??","answer":"Yes. Installation will be done by Lloyd authorised engineer. I paid 500 Rs. But it is totally depend on the engineer how much they want to charge for window AC installation","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"will you give us the installation","answer":"I paid 500 Rs. But it is totally depend on the engineer how much they want to charge for window AC installation","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Installation included in it??","answer":"No. You need to pay extra for installation. I paid 500/-","votes":"0","username":"Deepak","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it 100% copper ?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"AmazingSales17","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c0252"},"product_asin":"B09P5NCP8L","QAs":[{"question":"Alexa supports this ac or not?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nirav","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it will work with inverter afetr power cut","answer":"It can, if the inverter can output 15 amps ( starting current ) .","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they hae service provider in NCR region for afterward services ?","answer":"Worst service","votes":"0","username":"Nirav","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"1.00kw k meter mai chal jayega","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to check 360°","answer":"No one come for product presentation","votes":"0","username":"Nirav","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we require a stabilizer and if yes witthin what range of volt","answer":"Stabilizer Not required but our safety purpose, better to install voltage stabilizer in the range of 180v to 270v.","votes":"0","username":"VMS","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there an inbuilt stabilizer in this ac","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Akash jain","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stabilizer required for the ac. And if yes within what range?","answer":"Yes stabilizer required.... Use double booster voltage stabilizer for better performance","votes":"0","username":"VMS","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty of card how much time","answer":"Lloyd avoid to give warranty & told me to contact Amazon for same","votes":"0","username":"Nirav","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"In product information it says that batteries are not included. What battries are these?","answer":"2 nos. AA batteries for remote ARE included in the package.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya mai bahar se mechanic bulake installation kar sakta hun?","answer":"Nahi. Warranty void ho jayega.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which things in Installation kit? There are outdoor unit stand?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i do my won installation","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Comes with outdoor stand??","answer":"No. Outdoor stand.","votes":"0","username":"TJIKKO","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its delivered today, when they will come to install it?","answer":"2 -3 days.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation person is not responding from 2 days ? Why this bad service?","answer":"Call Lloyd customer service.","votes":"0","username":"R. VISWAS, from Mysore, in IND…","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who and when they will do installation?","answer":"From Lloyd company they send people for installation and after delivery done they will come within 48 hours","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Kumbhar","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it run on 240v?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it inverter?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who is responsible for installation?","answer":"Brand Havells","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is length of copper pipe come with ac","answer":"10ft","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the cost ?","answer":"30k","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty kitne time ki hai","answer":"1 year and 10 year for compressor","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"3 watt ke metter pr chal jayega","answer":"3 square mm pr chal jayega.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer Need","answer":"No,if ac volt available is between 180-270.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need any stabilizer for the ac?","answer":"Yes, you may need, but please don't buy this product. I had to return it, my installation expenses were not reimbursed. I had to face huge problems with this brand. Brand's customer care doesn't work at all. They only make false promises. Actually, I got incomplete product which was detected only after installing.","votes":"0","username":"Jalis Nasiri","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with copper pipe?","answer":"No pipe with the unit","votes":"0","username":"Rajkumar Lande","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper pipe kitna fit milega sathme installation ke liye","answer":"10 feet for both units.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation charges payable?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Include installation charge","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is 3 mtr copper wire included ?","answer":"Yes, along both of the units.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"The conneting copper pipes are missing what to do has to pay more for the missing copper standards pipes how to get refund for that","answer":"Simple, return the whole package back.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation cost of this AC","answer":"Approximate ₹1200-2000.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer requirements in this ac","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Lal Jat","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it coming up with WiFi controller ?","answer":"We have install App and setup on own","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"humicon mode which i see on the remote?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Isme extra pay kitna hota h","answer":"2500","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the cost of installation beyond standard installation (sq. Feet wise for copper wire and other materials used) ??","answer":"Depends areawise... App cost for stand 700 (wall stand) or 1000 (handing stand), 300 per sq feet for pipe ,wall drill charge extra may be app 1000 or 1500","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty of compressor for how much time","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"If any problem comes after installation or if any internal fault is detected then who will pay for installation","answer":"LLOYD engineer will look after that and reinstallation will be done by company","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What its power consumption?","answer":"746 watts","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation compulsory","answer":"No, Not at all","votes":"0","username":"A K SHARMA","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper wire missing :( what’s the resolution on this? Where should I file a complaint and how do I get reimbursed for the additional charge?","answer":"The company representative came for fitting open the packets no copper pipe he took extra ₹2250 fitted and said Amazon will refund ₹2250 but no process no one respond","votes":"0","username":"K Subbarao","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What Is the noise level inside and outside? Inside noise is just 32db?","answer":"Yes.. u will not hear any noise inside","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the waranty period for the condenser and indoor unit seperately? Is this fully copper condensor?","answer":"Yes copper condenser . 10 yrs","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Kumar","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"It works in winter also?","answer":"No it do not have heater in it","votes":"0","username":"palwinder","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f661cfba6a7877c025d"},"product_asin":"B08V8J5N7P","QAs":[{"question":"Two ton ac kitna area cool karega","answer":"Next level thanda karega buy it","votes":"0","username":"Amit","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f681cfba6a7877c0288"},"product_asin":"B09SGNMD7R","QAs":[{"question":"It can be install in varticaly","answer":"No as far as I know","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much down payment of windows ac","answer":"As per price quoted by amazon","votes":"0","username":"Indranil","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we added gst no","answer":"What you pay Amazon is the final price which would include GST","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to avail 1 year warranty on AC and 5 year warranty on the compressor??","answer":"You have to call service","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabiliser is necessary ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Indranil","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any need of stabilizer?","answer":"Preferable","votes":"0","username":"Indranil","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Indranil","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote will come with digital screen?","answer":"Yes, I received  it with digital screen","votes":"0","username":"GEET","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote is digital or not?","answer":"Yes it's degital","votes":"0","username":"Deepanshu","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need stabilizer..?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"CS","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Condensor is copper or aluminium?","answer":"It's copper","votes":"0","username":"Agamoni Ghosh","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product have remote control or not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RDigital","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size of ac for fitting in wall","answer":"Worst company and services.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is 2021 model expensive as compared to 2022","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Deepanshu","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"When would installation team from lloyd come?","answer":"My own arrangements..no call came from lloyds","votes":"0","username":"NAGENDRA BABU","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Urgent dilevery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"NAGENDRA BABU","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to free service","answer":"Chargeable","votes":"0","username":"Virendra Kumar","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why 2022 model 3 star is cheaper than 2021 model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Virendra Kumar","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the Installation fee? Can I get it installed by my own technician?","answer":"With own technician..cheaper 1000","votes":"0","username":"NAGENDRA BABU","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will install this ac? I have ordered this and collected this today. Now, who will install this?","answer":"You can contact customer care","votes":"0","username":"NAGENDRA BABU","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will install the AC?","answer":"Engeeneer","votes":"0","username":"Virendra Kumar","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"इसके लिए best stablizer konsa h","answer":"We have Candes purchased from Amazon too.","votes":"0","username":"CS","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation included in the price","answer":"Nope you have to pay extra for installment","votes":"0","username":"GEET","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges??","answer":"You can check it during ordering  of the ac.","votes":"0","username":"GEET","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will do the installation","answer":"The company guys will come & do the installation.","votes":"0","username":"CS","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I install it from outside?","answer":"Yes, I got it installed from outside. Amazon installation person did not respond for 4 days straight.","votes":"0","username":"Pranay","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model glw18b3ywses remote is simpe or digital","answer":"It is a simple one without any digital display. It is enough though.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f6a1cfba6a7877c0293"},"product_asin":"B09SGLJVLS","QAs":[{"question":"Power consumption for one hour","answer":"Can't really help u with that as could not keep the AC on for an hour... It cools the room really fast that too keeping the temperature at 24","votes":"0","username":"Deblina chatterjee","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation  process?","answer":"After delivery, call Havells and they will take care of the installation plus they’ll register your product for warranty too.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the stand for ac is provided","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer specificatoon with this modelA: Model no. …","answer":"No comments","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Technician for installation is not comming, they have cancelled my appointment. What happens if i get installed by myself?","answer":"Technician for installation four days installation","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the year of manufacturing?","answer":"Installation service is veryvery poor for that reason pls don't buy it brand","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SINGH","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stablizer in the box","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any need for steblizer for this model?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SINGH","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the remote have digital screen or not?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Manisha","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need stabilizer or not?","answer":"Needed","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SINGH","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use v guard  vnd 400 plus steplizer for this ac ?","answer":"Yes u can","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SINGH","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is bajaj finance - no cost emi payment mode is not available?","answer":"Online payment","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"How should i buy without paying gst as it is showing 2 price option with gst and without gst for business customers","answer":"GST payment","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shall we have to call for get installation for window AC","answer":"Yes","votes":"1","username":"Deblina chatterjee","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is power consumption per hour ?","answer":"I didn't see the wattage so can't tell you precisely but it consumes very less power.","votes":"0","username":"Anuradha Singh","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the max ampere or watts of electricity consumption on full load","answer":"1500 watt or 7 amps at 220 volt","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac fit both type horizontal and vertical  ?","answer":"Only horizontally","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use v guard  vnd 400 plus steplizer for this ac ?","answer":"Model no. VG400AE10 by v guard I am using. It is working fine.","votes":"0","username":"kumar…","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges free or not","answer":"Not free","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation","answer":"You have to pay","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges","answer":"Not free","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac have turbo button on ac and remote?","answer":"Only on remote","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Singh","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"minimum and  maximum temperature we can set","answer":"Minimum 16 Maximum 30!","votes":"0","username":"Sachin mishra","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this suitable for drain areas","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Sachin mishra","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this Ac support mobile App for remote function?","answer":"No .it doesn't support mobile app. As this AC is without wifi and bluetooth","votes":"0","username":"Shishir","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Services kitne time karni chaiye","answer":"Once a year","votes":"0","username":"Shesh Shukla","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will they provide installation including cutting and fixing of windows grill?","answer":"No.Installation is standard, that mean only installind the ac in pre formed frame or space. You have to do all other grill cutting and making space by local fabricators or carpentor. It is beneficial too, since if the do this also they will charge more than expected additional 1800 to 2000 over standard installation. Same work will cost you 1000 to 1200 from local fabricator includindg little bit of wooden piece ply etc.see less","votes":"0","username":"DR K.","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why my this ac is not drop water?","answer":"Check mode  on remote in which AC running, dry mode and dry weather( no humadity or very less humadity) did'nt make water to drop. If your AC is cooling well no matter to bother. Water from AC is totally dependent on humidity condition of weather, so no water from ac in dry hot conditions.","votes":"0","username":"DR K.","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f6b1cfba6a7877c02be"},"product_asin":"B08TB54NGQ","QAs":[{"question":"Does eco mode availabe in this ac?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vandhnasharma","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f6f1cfba6a7877c0306"},"product_asin":"B09G391BM1","QAs":[{"question":"Does we get coper wire and what is the length of itz","answer":"Small wire...","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have horizontal swing ? And wifi ?","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What kind of coil does it have, copper or aluminium? One of the reviews says it has aluminium coil","answer":"It has copper coil","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor pcb warranty","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i get GST input?","answer":"If you order from Amazon Business","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Price includes installation charges?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do i avail gst 28%","answer":"buy from Amazon buisness","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has 5 years PCB warranty?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on compressor is 5 or 10 year?","answer":"It's 10 Year","votes":"0","username":"Sacchidanand","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this work for 20 X 20 feet room?","answer":"It will be better to go for 2 ton capacity. For better cooling in peak sunmers","votes":"0","username":"Rana","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will cool in 45 digree 1.5 ton","answer":"I don't know because it's not even started after buying,so after 10 days of struggle and harrasment,i have got it return and i got refunded,","votes":"0","username":"rakesh kaushik","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f6f1cfba6a7877c030f"},"product_asin":"B08SW4FYZM","QAs":[{"question":"Is there any ggarenty or warenty in ac","answer":"Warranty","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it come with remote or not?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Erlin gozmao","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"what if ac is creating too much noise?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Erlin gozmao","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"is internal wifi provided in this ac","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Erlin gozmao","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"ac has auto restart system when power gone","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Erlin gozmao","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kia installment par uplabdh hai","answer":"Haan ji","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"when will be instalation will be done","answer":"As early as possible. They will call","votes":"0","username":"BHARATROHELLA","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this running without current","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Erlin gozmao","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Install charging at home","answer":"Its as per the brand policy","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of the wire?","answer":"1. 5 mtr","votes":"0","username":"Gourav Arya","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this come with stabilizer? What are and how much is the potential additional charges I have to incure.?... Replacement","answer":"No you have to buy the stabilizer from market.. it will cost around 2000. And in addition you have to pay installation charges around 500 - 1000.","votes":"0","username":"Mohit","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have stablizier inside ?","answer":"better to have one outside , if power fluctuates frequently.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it inverter ac or not? Reply from seller please with proof. immediate buy.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the date of manufacturing of product","answer":"Its 2022 model","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why this Ac bring so noise on above 20 temperature","answer":"Has to work harder.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length ,width, height of window ac","answer":"1.5 Feet x2. 5 feet","votes":"0","username":"Gourav Arya","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this sufficient for 210 sqft room size.","answer":"Yes, unless there is too much heat beating on the walls and roof. We used it in 290sq ft and its perfect","votes":"0","username":"Diy-er","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size of window required for installation","answer":"AC + size","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Seriol no kya hain","answer":"Sabka alag alag hai. Kharido toh pata chalega.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered AC and stablizer same time why delivered on different dates","answer":"May b different sellers","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered both stablizer and Air conditioner at same time why deliveey date is different","answer":"Alag co. ke honge","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"The AC has stopped working in just 1 month and 20 days after installation. I have already booked the complaint,its been more than 2 days its not fixed","answer":"Was it registered with Voltas immediately after you installation? Even otherwise a service request with them should work.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we install this in ventilation windows??","answer":"yes if window size is 80.5cm x 43cm","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product ok for which room size?","answer":"165 sq feet","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac with inverter technology","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is temperature range","answer":"16 to 35","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange old ac","answer":"Please check while buying on site","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"If I am ready to pay for installation then does Amazon offer this service?","answer":"No its Voltas who provide free installation but its misleading material required is chargeable","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"15 hours usage in a day. Units consumption approx??","answer":"22 units roughly","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"If it not fixed in the window then will it return or not?","answer":"No its not possible please check dimensions of window and AC first before you order","votes":"0","username":"Viresh Singh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we find out that it is an inverter ac","answer":"In normal AC we can hear the start Stop noise of compressor. In this AC We can't. Only compressor Speed increasing and decreasing noise can be heard.","votes":"0","username":"DC","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no inverter mentioned on ac","answer":"Nothing changes in inverter AC or non inverter AC. Only the compressor and PCB.","votes":"0","username":"DC","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much power supply need for 1.5 tan 5 star window ?","answer":"Depends on usage only. If you run this AC on 28 degree Celsius then only around 700 watts an hour and if you run on 20 degree Celsius then around Full wattage of 1.7 kilowatts.","votes":"0","username":"DC","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the correct dimensions of this product beacuse 80.5cm length is too big, even 1.5ton unit is 66cm in length..","answer":"dimension of 1.5 and 1.4 tone are same as standard","votes":"0","username":"SUBHASIS ROY","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this requires stablizier ?","answer":"Usually none. But if the power supply of your area fluctuates a lot then of course you need badly.","votes":"0","username":"DC","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Plz share the correct dimension of AC . There are many different answers to this question","answer":"call customer care.","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this all weather AC?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Hemant Kumar Pal","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether copper tubes are part of this AC","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hemant Kumar Pal","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"My window size is 68×45 (LxH). Will it fit in the window?","answer":"Not good cause power too much charge","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can U please provide the delivery at delhi pincode 110009?","answer":"I want to my window A C change","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does ‘fixed speed’ mean?","answer":"Fixed speed means it's not an inverter AC. This will consume more energy .","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the instlation charge for this AC?","answer":"Depends. If they have to cut grills etc then 1500, else 1000.","votes":"0","username":"Ankur Kumar","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought this AC last year, 2021, but it was installed by our electrician. Does it qualify for the yearly servicing?","answer":"No, your warranty is null and void now.","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"If exchange rejected can return the product","answer":"Yes ,, you can say  You are not satisfied with the performance, only if it's within the return period","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Campresar ki waranti hi","answer":"Hi Hi Hi bilkul hi","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust its cooling capacity? I mean cooling tonnage. If yes, then at what percentages we have options..","answer":"Not the way you mean to.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange my old AC , it power on but it doesn't cool ,can i exchange it ?","answer":"Amazon will help.","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"1.5 ton ac me koi garenty ya warenty h or isy fix krny waly jb ayengy to koi charge lagega","answer":"Fix karne wale charge lete hai yadi Amazon ne maaf na kiya ho","votes":"0","username":"D Bhatt","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote is available or not","answer":"Yes, Remote is available along with ac and it will be activate by call in the number written in the backside.","votes":"0","username":"Nikhil","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f701cfba6a7877c031a"},"product_asin":"B089D2666Q","QAs":[{"question":"1.5 टन ए सी अधिकतम कितने वाट बिजली लेता है?","answer":"1800 watt maximum","votes":"0","username":"akshay","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Coil type copper or aluminum?","answer":"it is copper coil","votes":"0","username":"mahesh bujji","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many watts?","answer":"5200 watts","votes":"0","username":"Arun","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या इस ac को चलाने के लिए स्टेप्लाइजर की आवश्यकता नहीं है","answer":"AC ko chalane ke liye steblizer ki jarurat hoti hai","votes":"0","username":"akshay","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f701cfba6a7877c0323"},"product_asin":"B07DB7HWZC","QAs":[{"question":"manufacture date of this ac which will be supplied to us? would it be of 2022 make?","answer":"Yes it is 2022","votes":"0","username":"RK","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f721cfba6a7877c0341"},"product_asin":"B07XV1CXHQ","QAs":[{"question":"How much maximum amp will take in starting","answer":"Read the Manual","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"The ac good but issue with remote . I had 2 ac's in the 2 remote are not working i had pain more then 1000 rs for past 1 yr so, think before buying","answer":"I bought 2 ACs and never had any problems","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get single unit indoor?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Biswajit","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the installation is not Free of cost??","answer":"Installation is done by 3rd party","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have need voltas 1 ton ac price?","answer":"Check with the Company Distributor","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the refrigerant type, in description, it says 410 and features says R32. Which is the correct one?","answer":"R-410, it's a mixture of R-125 & R-32","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of pipe come with it","answer":"1 metre.","votes":"0","username":"Biswajit","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f721cfba6a7877c0349"},"product_asin":"B079MD9LHP","QAs":[{"question":"batteries  included no ?","answer":"A pair of batteries cost 20 rupees. Hope the buying decision does not rely on this parameter.","votes":"0","username":"abhishek sejwal","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"2019 model hai yeh 2022 model ka kya price aa old maal vech rhe aa","answer":"Returned as old and damaged AC supplied by the seller instead of new and full amount refunded by Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Neetu gupta","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is this ac inverter or non inverter modele  dza 183","answer":"Non-inverter","votes":"0","username":"abhishek sejwal","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Has anyone bought this ac in 2022? which manufacturing year product will i get ?","answer":"Noisee hai","votes":"0","username":"Aman","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"There are 2 models.please clarify","answer":"Nousee","votes":"0","username":"Aman","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Window AC Mein stabilizer lagta hai ya nahin","answer":"Better use one just to be on the safer side.","votes":"0","username":"abhishek sejwal","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work on single phase?","answer":"Yes, all window ACs work on single phase.","votes":"0","username":"JRBhatia","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या इसमें वाईफाई सुविधा उपलब्ध है","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"sumit Kishor Singh","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f741cfba6a7877c035b"},"product_asin":"B079MNPXH7","QAs":[{"question":"What is the wattage? is this inverter type window ac?","answer":"No it is normal ac..but very good cooling","votes":"0","username":"sarvendra singh","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need stablizer for window ac?","answer":"YES IT GENERAL ELECTRONICS EQUIPMENTS REQUIRMENT AND DEPNED ON YOUR HOUSE POWER SUPPLY CONDITION","votes":"0","username":"SUBHASIS ROY","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 star and 3 star difference","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free ac service","answer":"2 free Ac service","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for top floor? I mean cooling is good for top floor?","answer":"Go for some other brand. I have faced issue where i have to fill the gas every year, which is costing me more to run the AC. So suggestions is go for some other brand","votes":"0","username":"Pravin kumar","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Voltas ac 1.5 ron window 5 star body size","answer":"Same as others","votes":"0","username":"ankit","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f751cfba6a7877c0362"},"product_asin":"B079PW7PMC","QAs":[{"question":"Does ac have sleep timer?","answer":"Yes it has.","votes":"0","username":"Debdutta","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f751cfba6a7877c0366"},"product_asin":"B00LWRFC1W","QAs":[{"question":"How many inch wide is it?","answer":"Dimensions 600x385x570 mm","votes":"0","username":"TRIDIB GHOSH","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which  year  product/ manufacturing  date ?","answer":"Feb 2021","votes":"0","username":"TRIDIB GHOSH","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f751cfba6a7877c0375"},"product_asin":"B084Q7JW2J","QAs":[{"question":"Is there spare parts available","answer":"Yes Voltas service","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f761cfba6a7877c0377"},"product_asin":"B089QD4PDH","QAs":[{"question":"Lenth of ac in inches","answer":"The product delivered without copper pipes and some other parts. When contacted Amazon customer care they confirmed to go ahead with purchase of the missing item and they will reimburse it. Bills sent to them throuh mail one and half month back, till date no response and no call back from them. Paid Rs 4000/- for the parts but Amazon not credited the amount and to my surprise no one from Amazon responded.Very very poor service and response from Amazon. I lost trust on them and stopped purchase from them.see less","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year of product?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have 400 square feet hall","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it come with installation kit like copper pipe and wiring","answer":"No, this has to come, but supplier missed it","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wattage consumption??","answer":"High","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maximum distance between indoor and outdoor units","answer":"6 ft","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper tube outlet on both sides possible in this model?","answer":"Yes it has Copper condenser and is 100% cooper","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have been dust filter","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"RS Cooltech","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f761cfba6a7877c037f"},"product_asin":"B09RFX1NKP","QAs":[{"question":"IS this made by India","answer":"Yes definitely india","votes":"0","username":"prakashsinh parmar","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What do you mean by fixed speed","answer":"Speed of compressor in INVERTER DESIGN IS VARIABLE AS PER LOAD. This results in little reduction in electrical bill.But in case of card failure, repair cost is much more.However in Fixed speed design, speed of compressor is fixed ireespective of cooling load. Repairs cost in case of breakdown are very less as compared to Inverter design.see less","votes":"0","username":"Bubrate","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac have Wi-Fi ?","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Priyesh Jagtap","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there stablizer with this ?","answer":"It is there in power supply...called SMPS..switching mode power supply.","votes":"0","username":"Bubrate","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Imported AC compressor or which parts?","answer":"I think indian compressor.","votes":"0","username":"Bubrate","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Major difference between 0.8 ton 1 ton bluw star split ac","answer":"Price!!If ur room is less than 120sqfeet u can go for 0.8ton considering bed, wardrobe consuming 30% of volume of the roomIf room is vacant then go for 1 ton acsee less","votes":"0","username":"Priyesh Jagtap","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f771cfba6a7877c0387"},"product_asin":"B08WLPZBG8","QAs":[{"question":"I got my product delivered today, do i need to raise a installation request","answer":"You can ask for a normal mechan for installation. There is no hard and fast rule , only thing to check is whether the condenser is working fine with the outlet of water to outside of the room.","votes":"0","username":"Yogender Singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation charge now in 2022?","answer":"1600","votes":"0","username":"Yogender Singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac k sath Wire kitna fit aata h","answer":"2 to 3 Ft","votes":"0","username":"gyaneshwar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it stablizer free ac or we have to use stavlizer","answer":"No Stablizrler reqd","votes":"0","username":"gyaneshwar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f781cfba6a7877c0397"},"product_asin":"B09RG2SZVX","QAs":[{"question":"Is it work in double phase ?","answer":"Yes, it is","votes":"0","username":"Sridhar","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you provide the accessories (brackets) required for outdoor unit installation or we need to buy separate ?","answer":"We need to buy it seperately","votes":"0","username":"Anand Rao","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the description about this item, mentions it as \"split ac with non-inverter compressor:\" ? is not a invertor ac?","answer":"This is a inverter AC","votes":"0","username":"Anand Rao","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Here nothing installation charges mention?","answer":"1800 for installation charges","votes":"0","username":"Anand Rao","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which gas in compressor","answer":"R32","votes":"0","username":"CP","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are copper pipes provided  with product?","answer":"Yes as standard length of 10 ft.","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Kumar Singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it RA32 refrigerant","answer":"It's R32","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj Kumar Singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Free installation provided","answer":"No i paid 2200/-","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC have dehumidifier","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warranty on pcb?","answer":"5","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on pcb?","answer":"5","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product include drain pipe in the package?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty how much","answer":"5","votes":"0","username":"Tarun Choudary","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Smart ac or not...can we operate with our phone","answer":"Not a smart air conditioner. You cannot control it with your phone.","votes":"0","username":"Yo Mamba","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f781cfba6a7877c03a2"},"product_asin":"B09RG461YQ","QAs":[{"question":"Please clarify about ac type invertor or non inverter in description?","answer":"It is a non inverter AC model.","votes":"0","username":"RAM MOHAN","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its a hot and cool Ac .","answer":"Both modes available in this product.","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is inverter ac.?","answer":"This is not a inverter. But consume power equivalent to inverter. Like a fixed speed compressor.","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this ac be installed in 200 sq ft room","answer":"Off course.. but take more time to cooling that area","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty? compressor warranty? product warranty?","answer":"This is not have a PCB. They provide only 1 year warranty on product and 5years compressor","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Really 3m copper pipe coming with this product or we have to buy extra?","answer":"3mt pipe and cover material including in this product.","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the warranty on PCB?","answer":"This is not have a PCB so no warranty. They only provide 1year on Product and 5years Compressor warranty.","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"tell me about its warranties?","answer":"1year on product and 5years compressor","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling in old AC mandatory for exchange ?","answer":"Non working ac also take exchange","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is that 3m copper pipe include in this box?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Kumari M","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are battery included in box from dealer or we need to buy from outside","answer":"Remote without Battery in this product","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it inverter or non inverter","answer":"Non inverter but working fine like inverter.","votes":"0","username":"Saiyed Badhulla H","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its a Non inverter Ac?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Kush Narang","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it inverter AC","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Kush Narang","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free or paid","answer":"Paid. Rs 1200 for installation","votes":"0","username":"Kush Narang","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f791cfba6a7877c03af"},"product_asin":"B09P79533V","QAs":[{"question":"Is service free?","answer":"Installation fee paid. I don't know about service","votes":"0","username":"Thippu sultan","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation accessories free with ac ?","answer":"30 feet copper wire and all accessories free ,","votes":"0","username":"jainul abdeen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"The installation kit( Copper pipe & cable) is not delivered with this product, please confirm whether it is included in this produt","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"vipul","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which brand compressor is used in ac","answer":"Blue star","votes":"0","username":"Pavan takasi","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Out door ?is  unit copper","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"BP-ENTERPRISES","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have both copper condensor and copper cooling coil","answer":"Yes both have copper coil","votes":"0","username":"BP-ENTERPRISES","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have blue fin protection layer in inner and compresser?","answer":"Yes it have blue fin protection inner","votes":"0","username":"Pavan takasi","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac is require stablizer","answer":"Stabiliser will be depend on your power stability if u are in mumbai it’s not required","votes":"0","username":"BP-ENTERPRISES","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac come with stabilizer and installation","answer":"No this AC don’t have stabiliser","votes":"0","username":"Syed Maksuda Ahmed","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f791cfba6a7877c03b9"},"product_asin":"B09RFDT8XR","QAs":[{"question":"There is high voltage fluctuation at my place. which stabiliser should i use and what is the working voltage range of this ac ?","answer":"Use original Blue Star stabilizer or V Gaurd are the best.","votes":"0","username":"G M SUBHASH BABU","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on PCB??","answer":"5 yrs","votes":"0","username":"DEALOFTIME","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to turn on wifi","answer":"There is no wi fi off the shelf. You have to talk to Blue Star to get it done","votes":"0","username":"DD","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have to buy a seperate stebilizer or product gives stabilizer for this product??","answer":"Inbuilt stabilizer is there, you can have stabilizer free operation if you do not have high voltage flactuation","votes":"0","username":"DD","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it four way swing?","answer":"two way automatic swing for vertical air flow, manual adjustment for horizontal air flow","votes":"0","username":"DD","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its hot and cold use","answer":"only cold","votes":"0","username":"DD","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about the installation process?","answer":"They will take forever to install the AC. Bluestar installation service is so bad. I waited for one month after requesting Ac installation in Bluestar, they said they were coming and they cancel every time and then I just booked urban company installation.","votes":"0","username":"Sanjana","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the airflow of this 2022 model? 2 ton 5 star ac?","answer":"very good","votes":"0","username":"Kishan Pratap","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much efficient it will be when placed in 650 sq ft area?","answer":"It will not be enough.","votes":"0","username":"Sanjana","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the working voltage range of this ac?","answer":"220","votes":"0","username":"P S Deshpande","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"It comes with filled gas or need to refill gas at installation time","answer":"It comes with gas but it ll be closed. Pls call for installation and they would do the necessary things.","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i get a GST invoice?","answer":"I m not sure about gst","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Working Voltage Range ?","answer":"Pls check with electrician","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is exchange offer available","answer":"Yes I bought the ac on exchange only","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product needs stebilizer","answer":"I am using an old stabiliser. But the wire in the indoor unit is small length","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty pcb","answer":"Not sure what is pcb","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many feet copper pipe free ? with this machine","answer":"It’s three meters","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have 4 way swing ?","answer":"There is a swing but not sure about four way","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is installation charges?","answer":"1500+gst","votes":"0","username":"Srinivasa","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"It comes with filled gas or need to refill gas at installation time","answer":"It comes duly filled with gas so that it can run immediately on installation. :=0","votes":"0","username":"Aapuchi","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7a1cfba6a7877c03c0"},"product_asin":"B09RG55LZX","QAs":[{"question":"How much is PCB warranty?","answer":"3years","votes":"0","username":"A Muralidharan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Made in China?","answer":"Hope so","votes":"0","username":"A Muralidharan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it auto temp adjusting?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"A Muralidharan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Digital indicator available or not","answer":"Yes, available","votes":"0","username":"A Muralidharan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about Installation charges?","answer":"INR 1500 Labour","votes":"0","username":"A Muralidharan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include stand to mount the fan of an ac,?","answer":"If by fan you mean the out door unit. Then yes it comes with a stand.","votes":"1","username":"Madman","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much ll cost including installation?","answer":"1600 minimum","votes":"0","username":"mahendra","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this include copper wire ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"mahendra","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stabilizer required here?","answer":"Most importantly","votes":"0","username":"mahendra","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about Installation charges?","answer":"Up to 2000","votes":"0","username":"mahendra","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold facility ?","answer":"Only cooling facility available. Its a air conditioner.","votes":"0","username":"Sandip","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7b1cfba6a7877c03d9"},"product_asin":"B09RDSZVGV","QAs":[{"question":"My room is 120 sq ft on the top floor and maximum temperature in my area 45 degree Celsius. Can a bluestar 1.2 ton ac cool down my room?","answer":"It can cool but the ac has to run the compressor more in mentaining the temp as direct sun light falls on your room .go with 1.5ton or if you go with this then the inverter feature will not do any help in your electricity bills .","votes":"0","username":"Satyabrata Shaw","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stablizer is required or not for this ac!!!","answer":"Stabilizer is required as per service persons.","votes":"0","username":"SUBHAJIT DINDA","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free?","answer":"No, I was charged with rs1500, and the worst installation was provided, i had to redo the whole installation again which costed me 2100(uninstall + reinstall)","votes":"0","username":"utkarsh","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its inverter Ac becuase u mention on boby","answer":"Mera reviews 0.80 ton ke liye tha,jo inverter AC hai.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get it installed from a local vendor. I hope that doesn't impact warranty","answer":"Yes you can, but you get free installation from manufacturer. You should get it installed from manufacturer only.","votes":"0","username":"Sahil Verma","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":".8 hot and cold split AC","answer":"Cold","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i have to buy outdoor unit stand separately or is included in 1500 rs installation?","answer":"Yes and electrical wire also of approx 200 rs/ MTR and extra pipe 250/MTR if required.","votes":"0","username":"A K Dwivedi","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Split ac with non-inverter compressor: low noise. affordable compared to inverter split acs!!!! is this inverter or non inverter","answer":"This is with inverter","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Joshi","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"May i know the size of compressor l x w x h","answer":"On the box","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work with alexa?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Alok tripathi","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Odu stand included in installation","answer":"Ni","votes":"0","username":"Alok tripathi","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have blue fin protection?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Alok tripathi","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about installation?","answer":"Provide by company","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges ????","answer":"1500 +gst","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long the connection pipe they provide free of cost while installing?","answer":"3.5 m","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Bro is k sath ac ka10 foot pipe bhi ata he kya copper ka","answer":"Ys it comes as an standard.. 10 ft.","votes":"0","username":"Suraj Sharma","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where we will buy the stand for outdoor unit?","answer":"Amazon or your local market","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it ok for top floor room of size 110 sqft","answer":"Up to 100 Feet will give better performance","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Joshi","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"can I hv outdoor unit vertical","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be good for kitchen?","answer":"Of course","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Joshi","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is product under 10 year warranty?","answer":"Compressor","votes":"0","username":"amarjeet chohan","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"how much long copper pipe included with ac ?","answer":"Up to 10 feet","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Joshi","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb guarantee kitene sal ki he","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"amarjeet chohan","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Good for 11*11 feet room?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much copper pipe drainage pipe are you provide ?","answer":"3 plus meters","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"pcb warranty","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it 2020 model or 2022 model?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"for top floor & 81 square feet room it work well?","answer":"It will work. There should not be Gaps in Windows and doors. Rated for 100 Sq feet. I am using for 130 sq feet but room is on Ground floor in 2 storied house. It is giving very Quick Cooling","votes":"0","username":"Girish Magal","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it necessary to install service experts","answer":"Company deputed Agency must for first time Installation. Otherwise warranty will be void","votes":"0","username":"Girish Magal","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper pipe included in box","answer":"Yes, copper pipes & water drain pipe of approx 2 m (6 feet) in included in the box.","votes":"0","username":"Sabyasachi B.","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get 2022 model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"With Copper pipe, drainage pipe, outdoor unit stand nuts?","answer":"Yes they are supplied with unit.","votes":"0","username":"Girish Magal","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"2020 or 2022 model , which one will be delivered?","answer":"According to description","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this unit comes with copper pipe? and how much length?","answer":"Yes, Upto 10 Feet","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Joshi","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power consumption? Watts?","answer":"Normal","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is their installment process","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get 2022 model? if i order now?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get 2022 if i order now?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Brajesh Kumar","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have received ac, do i have to book installation request?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"digendra singh","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty is it applicable for outside installation","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"digendra singh","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require an establiser ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"digendra singh","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much are the installation charges, bluestar local service center called and informed charge 1650 plus. and we do not have thoption to self install","answer":"33%off through blue star aap","votes":"0","username":"digendra singh","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which Model i will get now 2022 or other","answer":"Don't buy this ac buy 1 ton nahi non inverter instead of this one","votes":"0","username":"digendra singh","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought the AC from amazon so how does it fit. Who comes to fit this ?","answer":"The service provider in your area will contact you after delivery of your ac","votes":"0","username":"Satyabrata Shaw","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"It requires 3 core wiring or 4 core wiring ?","answer":"3 core","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7b1cfba6a7877c03e9"},"product_asin":"B09RFCGW4X","QAs":[{"question":"Does it works in low voltage?","answer":"It turned off in my case.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold AC?","answer":"No heater","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have heating mode","answer":"No it doesn't have heating mode .!","votes":"0","username":"Radhakrishnan M","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has wifi connectivity if not then which ac does","answer":"You can search by keyword wifi. You will find one","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there horizontal swing?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep Thakur","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange my old ac???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it gave inverter compressor","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is inverter ac or normal ac. Because in discription noware it is mentioned","answer":"Inverter","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep Thakur","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac with dual inverter compressor?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep Thakur","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why it's not dispatched","answer":"They said stock not available","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days it will come","answer":"5 days","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered 1.5 ton ac on dated 30 th june .how many days it will come to reach my home . please send immediately because of rainy season will be","answer":"This question you should ask Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's manufacturer warranty for PCB?","answer":"Check product description","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Description says 2 Ton and 3 star. Please update the right description since it's confusing","answer":"Pls ask Amazon to update the product description","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"He is operate from mobile","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Titus Prakash","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty mention nhi hai  so koi certificate milega buy karne ke bad?","answer":"Yes, they give warranty confirmation via work order copy","votes":"0","username":"Vikas Chugh","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is their any temperature display on ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stablizer is required","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vikas Chugh","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"सर्दी में रूम हीटर का आनंद देगा","answer":"No..its only for summer","votes":"0","username":"Saba Ansari","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installtion free or paid?","answer":"Paid 1500","votes":"0","username":"Manikandan Govindan","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free???","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Manikandan Govindan","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"is cooper ware free?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Manikandan Govindan","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there light on remote display?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 4 way?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"gyaneshwar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is drain pipe not included when buying this ac??","answer":"It is included but short. Approx 70 cm","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7c1cfba6a7877c03f5"},"product_asin":"B0876SVTN8","QAs":[{"question":"Is this All weather ac, hot and cold both?","answer":"They have dilevered a wrong outdoor unit . It was supposed to be hot and cold but we received a normal one","votes":"0","username":"Nishant K.","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7d1cfba6a7877c03f7"},"product_asin":"B09R29RSFH","QAs":[{"question":"is pm 2.5 filter washable ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sivakumar Sucheendren","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it an old model or 2022 model, how to verify it?","answer":"Verify with the model #","votes":"0","username":"Sivakumar Sucheendren","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC have Dehumidifier feature?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sujit K.","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we run it for continuously 8 to 10 hours in a store?","answer":"I am not running it in a store but at home it continuously runs for 10 to 13 hours every day maybe more.","votes":"0","username":"Anju Bharadwaj","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it coming with complete installation kit now? I mean copper pipes and wires etc? I am seeing a lot of comments that say installation kit is absent","answer":"Only copper pipe coming along with AC. Other materials like extra pipe, power wire, plug and outdoor unit stand we need to pay at the time of installation","votes":"0","username":"Saipushkal","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about cooling capacity and air flow CFM","answer":"Hey Mate, I can't talk explicitly in CFM but I can just tell experienced/ felt Cooling Capacity and Air Flow- it is actually quite nice. 1.5 Ton would sufficiently cool the entire drawing room in a couple of initial minutes itself and it really is sufficient at 26-28 only even outside is 35+. Now about AirFlow, in this model, there are different Air Flow controls available but we always Operate at Auto which decides the best for the moment and keep maintaining the same for longer time. Hope this helps!see less","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Joshi","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"1 hour mai kitna energy legi","answer":"Depends on room temperature and ac cooling degree","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Power input from  outdoor unit?","answer":"Indoor unit to outerdoor unit","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many units it takes per hour ??","answer":"Room temperature and ac cooling degree","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cant this product be used without alexa or other ai tools","answer":"May be no","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer Free Operation 100-290v, is it true?","answer":"They claim it. but I'll suggest to use a voltage stabilizer because when voltage goes low output of ac also get affected and doesn't give proper cooling.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"auto cleaning options","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the function of Clean button on remote?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a hot and cold split ac?  does it work as a heater also??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mohan singh parihar","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Bajaj emi card posible or not?","answer":"Posible","votes":"0","username":"Mohan singh parihar","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i use heat mode in winters also?","answer":"No.. cooling only","votes":"0","username":"DINESH YADAV","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Interconnecting pipe for ac missing because i read in answers","answer":"Copper pipe is there in the box.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Interconnecting pipe for ac included??","answer":"Yes ...pipes are included","votes":"0","username":"Patrik D. Dhopte","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model ?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Pratik Joshi","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has Turbo cool","answer":"Yes. Has power chill option.","votes":"0","username":"RB","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"In the pic it says 2021 model, will we get 2021 model or 2022 model on ordering it?","answer":"You will get 2021 on ordering it","votes":"0","username":"Veerendra singh","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with copper kit for installation?","answer":"I didn't receive it, although it is printed on the packing that it includes the copper kit. I had to raise the concern with Amazon and they compensated around Rs 2800 as Amazon credits (not in cash). Btw, the service engineer had charged over 3000 for the copper kit.","votes":"0","username":"Sam David","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this Ac cool a 250 sq.ft room?","answer":"No, not recommended for this big room. Go for 2 Ton or above","votes":"0","username":"Subrata Ghosh","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Made in China","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"yusuf","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is indoor unit is copper ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Narayana Kobaka","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model 2022 ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Narayana Kobaka","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to apply for refund of missing items","answer":"Call Amazon customer care at the time of installation","votes":"0","username":"Veerendra singh","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is minimum temperature and maximum temperature?","answer":"Min16 °cmax 30,°c","votes":"0","username":"Veerendra singh","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to work with OK Google","answer":"I have received the ac with missing parts and same is informed to Amazon and Panasonic...Amazon suggested me for ask job sheet from Panasonic of missing item but Panasonic denied to visit and said ask from Amazon of missing parts...than again i have contacted to Amazon and explain all details than Amazon person check order details from lead I'd and confirm copper pipe and connecting wire is included in your order so they have escalated the matter to Panasonic with my job id...but after 3 days no one contacted to me from Panasonic...and my AC is still uninstalled...pls helpsee less","votes":"0","username":"ekta","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jow much will be the installation charges?","answer":"it will be 1100+gst","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Chauhan","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warrranty board & compresser","answer":"Five years on PCB (Printed circuit board) and ten years on compressor.","votes":"0","username":"Rupnarayan Singh","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Q: Will it be suitable for 190sqft room?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i got copper pipe with this ac and how much copper pipe I will received with this ac","answer":"As per box content 2 pipes and a cable is supplied.","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Including indoor outdoor copper pipe","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shivam Sharma","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Energy consumption is not showing in Miraie app, can someone help with fixing?","answer":"Make sure the AC is connected to WIFI while it running. Then only it can be able to show the power consumption estimates. Also, the data will be available after only 3 days","votes":"0","username":"john prem kumar","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I move the vertical flaps manually to right side ?","answer":"No vertical flaps","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"wifi not working with smart wifi button?","answer":"Press and hold wifi button on remote control, you will see SE on AC display then connect to router or hotspot and then app.","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer needed?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shivam Sharma","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are this a.c is Auto convertable","answer":"Yes. Fully Auto convertible for saving energy and providing optimal cooling at the same time.","votes":"0","username":"Rupnarayan Singh","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit stand","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shivam Sharma","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why Miraie app doesn't show energy consumption?","answer":"App is showing energy consumption","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper Wire and other pipes are included in this","answer":"On a box clearly mentioned get connecting cable and two numbers of copper pipes is supplied with this AC, when installation was started installation guy told me that 2 pipes and connecting cable wire missing so I return this air condition","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is in the box ? ur not mention copper  pipe","answer":"10 feet coper pipe is there in the box but if length will increase technician will charge extra for that","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Parshuram Dalbanjan","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is in the box ?  ur not mention coper  pipe","answer":"On a box content it's clearly mention that remote control batteries to copper pipes and a connecting cable","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I adjust the vertical flaps to left/right manually ?","answer":"No vertical flap","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether it has autocleen technology?","answer":"Yes they written this, but I had not tried yet","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Parshuram Dalbanjan","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Water pipe including?","answer":"no extra 5 ft 300","votes":"0","username":"piyush","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they provide GST invoice ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Bk","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get a gst invoice?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Bk","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Many reviewers mentioned Missing copper pipe inside the box? Why is that the case?","answer":"Yes it is missing do not buy","votes":"0","username":"Bk","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many packing box is being sent for delivery of this unit of AC","answer":"Packing box is brand provided, as per box content cable aneld 2 copper pipes supplied but it was missing during installation.","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper connecting pipe supply in box?","answer":"Supplied as per box content but it was missing,please see the photo of a installation agency, he has mentioned in job sheet.","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need to buy stabilizer??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Lalit Singh","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include installation ki?","answer":"No, Rs 999 for stand+Rs1300 for installation charge","votes":"0","username":"Lalit Singh","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maximum degree celcius in which the ac will work? Like other companiyes claim that the ac will work at 52degree celcius","answer":"30","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with a self clean function?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Bk","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"LG or Panasonic in 1.5 Ton with 5 star rating?","answer":"LG","votes":"0","username":"Bk","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do we distinguish between 2020 model and 2022 model ? Whats the grammar of the model No. ?","answer":"Brother please please please don't buy from amazon, i purchased on april 7, delivered on on 10 april...but it was delivered without some pipes so i requested to return but no one is coming to pick up this. Today april 26 but no any response, called many times to amazon but no any solution and they says..our higher authority working on it...but no any pick up for return, pick up cancelled 6 times but amazon is not taking care.see less","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this have jet stream ???","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Parshuram Dalbanjan","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling capisity","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Parshuram Dalbanjan","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be suitable for 180sqft room?","answer":"Yes if you have a tight room then it's okay","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i buy ac from amazon and installation is done by non company person will warranty be valid","answer":"Warranty must be valid","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Indoor outdoor copper connection pipe not available in the box.","answer":"In my case proper connection pipe was not supplied that's why I returned this","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please help pipe is not available inside the box","answer":"If pipes not in the box ask the instruction guys to give you a job seat which indicates or confirms that copper pipes were not supplied in the box but the content shows it's supplied then you can return this item or purchase it from installation guy and the payment will be done by Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation  kit available","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"ROBIN THOMAS","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"it have a nano x/nano g","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ROBIN THOMAS","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I spoke with ac installation person today.  he said that if you have purchased ac  from amazon then  copper pipe not include inside the box","answer":"10 meters is included call the panasonic helpline directly to lodge complaints installation is done by agencies appointed by panasonic and they always scam customers.","votes":"0","username":"Saumil Gajaria","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation person ask copper pipe not include can you please help copper pipe is available inside the box?","answer":"copper pipe included in the box. However, we need to pay for wire, drain pipe and stand which is not included. I already had the entire setup done few years ago only had not installed AC. I was charged INR1300 only for AC installation. Check the rate for piping and stand from outside. I reckon AC guy informed me that piping is 300rs per mtr and 100rs per inch for core cutting.see less","votes":"0","username":"Maharshi","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any delivery charges?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ROBIN THOMAS","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much copper pipe is included in the purchased product ?","answer":"10 Feet","votes":"0","username":"Dr. Sanjeev Kumar Lale","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why installation kit is not there with the AC ?","answer":"Instalation kit is  there","votes":"0","username":"ROBIN THOMAS","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to installehat is the cost for installation","answer":"1360","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much cost for outdoor unit stand?","answer":"Outdoor understand rupees 799","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac pack come with Wall mount stand for Outdoor unit","answer":"No. You have to purchase it separately.","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I order this product 2nd time and i am getting only indoor unit from the sell. What kind of service you are providing to your customers.","answer":"I returned full AC set, cause no pipes were supplied, now i got full refund of ₹40,990/- and AC is still not picked up by Amazon","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Wifi switchblade on/off? Or it stays on all the time?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dr Javed Ahmad","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper wire for indoor n outdoor connection available with 2022 model","answer":"Yes it is. A limited length and if more needed you have to pay for it separately.","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Idu to odu copper pipe supplied length?","answer":"Length should be 10 metre","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with auto clean function ? 🤷","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Including 3 mater coper pipe and wire","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vipul vankar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model has jet stream feature ?","answer":"Yes, but I am told using this feature is avoidable if you care for the long life of the airconditioner.","votes":"0","username":"Genuine feedback, no bias.","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model has jet stream feature ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Darling","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"hot and cold ac","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Chauhan","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do both Condenser and heat exchanger (outdoor unit) both are cooper tube only qualified person answer.","answer":"Condensor coil of outdoor unit is copper but the fins are of aluminium.","votes":"0","username":"Genuine feedback, no bias.","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it works on inverter","answer":"Don't but from amazon.. I ordered on 29/03/22 till today they didn't deliver the order and no response from these people.. Go for flipkart.","votes":"0","username":"Vinay Madhav","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product has copper pipe included in the box?","answer":"Yes it comes","votes":"0","username":"HARSHA","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Per hour how many units of pover it will take","answer":"It depends on difference between outside temperature and opted temperature set to ac along with other optional features. If ac set to 24°c taking all other system in normal optimisation then average consumption will be less than 1unit/hr.","votes":"0","username":"Rupnarayan Singh","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are the accessories packed inside the box? I received the a/c but yet to open it.","answer":"Yes the accessories were present inside the box.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Steblaisre is needed?","answer":"No separate stabiliser is required, unless you demand for it.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be good enough for 220 sq ft ?","answer":"I believe it should work.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why so expencive on your app  ? In market its price 40900 rs only we also trust amzon app but some time some product came very high price","answer":"Price is indeed variable from time to time. Also, point to be noted that, installation charges, core cutting, grill framing, etc. may lead upto additional ₹4500/- approx.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stand is required for out door unit ?","answer":"Yes. Better to go for iron framing mounted on the wall.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much lenght pipe is provided along with this unit? Is stabilizer included?","answer":"Not sure about the actual length, however it’s sufficient enough if not far away from the outdoor unit.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will warrenty cover if we install with our known person","answer":"If it’s for free, then it’s a good option, else better to go for the paid services by Panasonic service engineers (may read as staff) only.","votes":"0","username":"Nabarun Choudhury","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7e1cfba6a7877c0403"},"product_asin":"B09RN6WQHF","QAs":[{"question":"For what room size is it ideal","answer":"for 10*15 size it is superb","votes":"0","username":"Avinash","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer free  with ac","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Avinash","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it connect to home wifi on 5GHz or 2.4GHz radio? i use airtel 5GHz wifi at home.","answer":"I connect it with Jio dongle. I connect  it with my mobile wifi also. Works well.","votes":"0","username":"gagnesh","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 year varanty on both indor and outdor pcb??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Avijeet","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"this ac causes damage to ozone layer","answer":"Yes very bright one","votes":"0","username":"Parbati ghosh","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it have temprhur display","answer":"Yes very bright one","votes":"0","username":"Parbati ghosh","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its available with silver outdoor in open market. Why are you selling with white one ?","answer":"It is silver","votes":"0","username":"Avijeet","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much energy it consumes for 8 hrs ?","answer":"Never measured but bill is low when compared to my previous ac","votes":"0","username":"Avijeet","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"My ac is maintaining room temperature how to turn off that feature? After cooling it automatically starts increasing temperature","answer":"May be your remote issue but it's better to talk with Panasonic","votes":"0","username":"Parbati ghosh","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many free services are there in what period of time?","answer":"You wl get two visit for cleaning purpose","votes":"0","username":"Parbati ghosh","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i get multiple split ac of this model . Need shipper response","answer":"Ask suppier","votes":"0","username":"Avijeet","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7e1cfba6a7877c040e"},"product_asin":"B09R3XHPVZ","QAs":[{"question":"Please tell me what maximum temperature can be outdoor when ac can still work i.e 48 , 50, 52 or more.","answer":"Up to 52 degrees","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Patel","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it necessary to install from company technician?","answer":"I think No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"My room size is 210 square feet so 1.5 ton is sufficient?","answer":"For better cooling 2 Ton is recommended.","votes":"0","username":"CHAKRINI INFO SYSTEMS","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"If you buy this a / c, will the fixing service company come?","answer":"You have call the the company for installation and they will charge for installation","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i be getting ac indoor unit bracket along with the ac itslef.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"shubham vivek","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac remote stopped working within 15days..now how to get the replacement??","answer":"Contact Company for warranty service","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model hot and cold","answer":"Yes its low as 16 degree, and high at 32 degree. But its so cool with 24 degree that its not required to turn low. It has a super sensor inside which understand the outside and inside temperature and adjust the cool automatic.","votes":"0","username":"Debaditya Dasgupta","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation including in order?","answer":"Yes. Installation charge 799 +gst","votes":"0","username":"Naba Jyoti Gogoi","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this model (2022, 1.5 ton 3 star ac) wifi is available or not?","answer":"Not working wifi","votes":"0","username":"Ripal Shah","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it 2 way auto swing or 4 way auto swing?","answer":"2-Way","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Agnihotri","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please confirm if it comes with extra copper wire in the box.","answer":"No extra copper wire including it","votes":"0","username":"Naba Jyoti Gogoi","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you adjust the tonnage (convertibility ) manually?? Or its only automatic","answer":"No we can not adjust tonnage","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Cooper pipe included with ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Naba Jyoti Gogoi","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much is installation","answer":"Cost is about 1500","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many free preventative service in the first year?","answer":"Totally 3 servicing","votes":"0","username":"Debaditya Dasgupta","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this neno technology?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ripal Shah","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do i make it to work at a set temperature? my newly bought ac works at lower temperature than the set temperature & breaks my sleep","answer":"Not to buy thia as wrist service by PANASONIC TEAM, ALAO THE PERFORMANCE IS NOT UP TO THE MARK LIKE daikin AND HITACHI","votes":"0","username":"Ripal Shah","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the delivery person will remove the existing ac as i bought this on exchange basis? if they remove it, how much they charge for removing ?","answer":"No they had not removed","votes":"0","username":"Ripal Shah","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper pipe included…?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Naba Jyoti Gogoi","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered it on 16 April and after 6 days it has not been shipped","answer":"Call customer care of amazon","votes":"0","username":"Ripal Shah","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I have an exchange offer","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I have a exchange offer on this ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation cost ?","answer":"Almost 1500","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a remote control","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with 3 meter copper pipe n electrical wire in 2022 April model","answer":"Yes but not measured","votes":"0","username":"Sudhir Mehrotra","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Copper pipe include","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sudhir Mehrotra","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this include 3 meter copper tubing with wire??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anuj George","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it support auto restart after power cut?","answer":"Yes, support previous mode apply after power cut","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much do you charge for installation? What materials included in it?","answer":"2399 something","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation kit included? And what is the length of copper tube and other things.","answer":"1 kit including the main contain box, 12-15 feet pipe and wire avelable","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many services free with this model?","answer":"Grnal","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use this AC in winters??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the minimum voltage required to run this Ac","answer":"190-240V","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gst  invoice","answer":"Yes avelabel","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"8 hours  unit","answer":"12-15 unit","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether non inverter type AC available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many free services in the first year?","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"Ratan Lal jatiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Evaporator fins aluminium or copper ?","answer":"Aluminium","votes":"0","username":"Anuj George","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"which V-guard stabilizer works best with this AC in kerala","answer":"I am using without stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"SH!V","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7e1cfba6a7877c0419"},"product_asin":"B09R248ZWX","QAs":[{"question":"Is it with air purifier facility?","answer":"Every air conditioner has an air filter.","votes":"0","username":"Joseph","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total units consumption in 1 hour?","answer":"5 unit","votes":"0","username":"Shailika Srivastava","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if I want the copper tube length longer as the location requires?","answer":"You will have to pay extra.","votes":"0","username":"Joseph","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can use stablizer in this","answer":"Yes you can use stabilizer but i dont have as electricity is ok in our area no fluctuations .so it depends on your","votes":"0","username":"Geeta Bisht","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"While buying the total cost is coming as 37240 rs , maybe because I have prime . I want to confirm if thats inclusive of installation?","answer":"No installation is 1200. 999+ gst. Plus extra charges of the things which would be required during installation.","votes":"0","username":"Pradipta Maity","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have heat mode ??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi Nath","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Room size 14 by 12 ft 1 ton Panasonic will do?","answer":"As per my experience this AC is suitable for 10 by 10..for 14 by 12 room, it will work but does not give the best performamnce..better to go with 1.5 ton machine.","votes":"0","username":"Abhijeet Raokhande","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Air flow 4 way","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nidhi Nath","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"how to contact panasonic for installation.?","answer":"They will contact you after delivery","votes":"0","username":"Joseph","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the compressor cut off at desired room temperature","answer":"In auto mode","votes":"0","username":"Joseph","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are Installation accessories provided in box?","answer":"In my case, the copper pie and power cable were missing. Raised this to Amazon who promptly refunded the amount I had to spend extra in installation.","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh M","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is on pcb 5 year warrenty pcb means?","answer":"It is board inside indoor unit which comes in inverter AC","votes":"0","username":"VISHAL DILIP SHEVALE","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Number of free services?","answer":"I’m still waiting for my free serviceThey were supposed to do 3 freeServices but no contactDue to covid and post that alsosee less","votes":"0","username":"JEEV","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the compressor need to be plugged from outside or from inside?","answer":"Compressor is attached to the AC unit. Doesn't need to be plugged separately","votes":"0","username":"Nimisha","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have old ac but not cooling can be exchange.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"VISHAL DILIP SHEVALE","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Connecting  pipe including in box","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vijoy Kumar Prasad","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get it installed from from regular service man??","answer":"No if you do that you want get the warranty","votes":"0","username":"Geeta Bisht","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maximum temperature of atmosphere; within which the aircon can work?","answer":"48","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the maximum temperature of atmosphere within which the aircon can work?","answer":"49 degrees centigrade","votes":"0","username":"Vijoy Kumar Prasad","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work on 50 degree outside  temperature ?","answer":"in Ahmedabad my ac is working super cool even at 27 c ac setting, in Ahmedabad right now temperature is 44 degrees Celsius, I think it will work well in proper packed, insulated room even at 50 degrees Celsius, 1 ton inverter ac is ideal only for 120sq area, away from heavy direct sunlight facing room","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh Sharma","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac require external device to connect to wifi or is it inbuilt","answer":"Wifi is inbuilt in it. You can connect it with you Alexa or google home or you phone.","votes":"0","username":"Diwakar Rana","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Outdoor unit stand is in Box?","answer":"No better buy from outside local store will be around Rs500 to Rs600","votes":"0","username":"kashif zaman","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Connecting pipe kit included in box ? If yes thn how much length","answer":"yes. connecting pipe included in the box. 2 meters","votes":"0","username":"ADAM M S HAMEED","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it have low gas detection feature?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Badrinath R.","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Cooling capacity?","answer":"One T","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"3mtr Copper pipe is available or not in this Unit ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Panasonic 1 ton split ac is dual inverter ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"My Ac Automatically changes settings. Any way to fix this?","answer":"Try to off the sleep mode","votes":"0","username":"Diwakar Rana","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are services free within 1 year warranty?","answer":"yes, everything","votes":"0","username":"Avdhesh Yaduvanshi","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7f1cfba6a7877c0424"},"product_asin":"B09RP8GB52","QAs":[{"question":"Is remote equipped with back light?","answer":"no it isn't","votes":"0","username":"Riya Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is invater ac or normal ac ?","answer":"normal","votes":"0","username":"Riya Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f7f1cfba6a7877c0435"},"product_asin":"B09R4G1ZNJ","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have a display? I can't see it on the picture","answer":"Yes, it does.","votes":"0","username":"SK","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"GST invoice available?","answer":"As per Amazon, if you need GST invoice, the order has to be placed thru business account. From regular account GST invoice is not issued. At least i could not get GST invoice for this product.","votes":"0","username":"Jitendra","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product Warranty","answer":"1 year product warranty, 5 years PCB and 10 yr. compressor","votes":"0","username":"Keyur Patel","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it Include connection pipe with wire??","answer":"Yes, it does. For ac to power plug, you have to get the wire.","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer is mandate for this or not?","answer":"If there is more voltage fluctuations at your locality, then go for voltage","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi, the installation guy is saying the copper wire is just 3m and no drainage pipe included , can u confirm ?","answer":"You are fortunate that installation guy is telling you and probably not charging you 3 m of copper wire also. In my case I paid for everything (material) used except for labour cost which was not charged to me.","votes":"0","username":"AmazonCustomer","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many area covered","answer":"It covers the 200sq ft living room","votes":"0","username":"Kaybee","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Out door auto off","answer":"Its inverter based AC, outdoor unit cutoff will be based on the indoor temperature. Unlike normal AC which turn off outdoor frequently, Inverter ACs will not turn off quiet often","votes":"0","username":"Kaybee","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter or non inverter ac","answer":"It’s inverter AC","votes":"0","username":"Gagan","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this include copper pipe for connecting indoor and outdoor units . In offline market they orovide 10 feet of capper pipe with ac.","answer":"Yes it is included inside packing","votes":"0","username":"AshishG","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hidden display in 1.5 ton AC can be displayed in any area","answer":"Only in Center","votes":"0","username":"Maitreya Deb","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is highest temperature that ac works on?","answer":"Cooling wise its okay I have tested it in 37 degree","votes":"0","username":"Maitreya Deb","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have to buy ac. Can you make a hole through beam.","answer":"Not recommended.","votes":"0","username":"SK","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product available with gst invoice","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"SK","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac comes with nanoe technology?","answer":"NO.","votes":"0","username":"Maitreya Deb","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"4 way swing available ?","answer":"Auto vertical, manual horizontal.","votes":"0","username":"SK","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper connecting pipes providing in the box?","answer":"Yes it has.","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is not mentioned that copper pipe is included or not & what is length of copper pipe included in 2022 model?","answer":"Though it's not mentioned, i recieved it with in the box. And length was around 2.5-3 meter","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model have wifi support?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Customer…","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f801cfba6a7877c044d"},"product_asin":"B09R45Q5WP","QAs":[{"question":"There is no need of voltage stabilizer to run this","answer":"YeS, true no need for that","votes":"0","username":"Faraaz Farshori","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"does this AC have a hand operable remote ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vidya","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it cool and hot both ?","answer":"This is a cooling airconditioner.","votes":"0","username":"vidya","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about installation","answer":"The team from Panasonic will contact you within 24-48 hours for the installation. In case you are not contacted, you can leave a note on Amazon. The guys from Amazon will also contact you for the installation, but please be aware that this will be done by a local electrician and you will not get a warranty by Panasonic.","votes":"0","username":"vidya","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought this ac yesterday  but  connecting copper pipe is missing what should i do now","answer":"Most of the items related to the installation will be brought by the Panasonic installation guy. The team will call you to understand your requirements (if you need to drill extra holes, stabilizer, extra copper pipe etc), you can tell them on call about this issue. If anything is missing, the installation guy will arrange.","votes":"1","username":"vidya","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much lowest temperature ac will go","answer":"16","votes":"0","username":"Nikhil","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Waterproof Compressor","answer":"What I did get question","votes":"0","username":"Nikhil","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f811cfba6a7877c0472"},"product_asin":"B09RKBM3XV","QAs":[{"question":"Gst bill","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Smart World Jaipur","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"850 units per year  , means how many  hours used per day","answer":"8 hours per day","votes":"0","username":"Smart World Jaipur","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Panasonic sac 1.5t 5sinv zu18ykyf","answer":"Nice product.  Though bit expensive but very good performance during 1st Month. On time delivery and installation by supplier Alap Electronics. Can't comment much since usage period is less , but","votes":"0","username":"Dhanraj","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote with led?","answer":"The remote glows with all the details visible even in the dark(Only when in use).","votes":"0","username":"Tejas Naik","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Operating temperature in remote?","answer":"16 to 28","votes":"0","username":"Dhanraj","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it have the ocb 5 years warranty","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dhanraj","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Include copper pipe???","answer":"Yes. approx. 3mtr.","votes":"0","username":"Mudit Singh","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cantrol.method.meaning","answer":"Remote, Panasonic App, Alexa and Google assistant","votes":"0","username":"Dhanraj","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac use  without Steblizer","answer":"This is a Inverter AC, so no stabilizer required.","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its hot and cold","answer":"only cold.","votes":"0","username":"Mudit Singh","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"auto-clean feature available ?","answer":"Yea","votes":"0","username":"Abhimanyu Vyas","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges?","answer":"Thousand rupees. Plus stand/pipe charges additional.","votes":"0","username":"Abhimanyu Vyas","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this have heat mode for winter","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mudit Singh","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hello is this model an online only or even available offline stores?","answer":"No, it is available both Online and in store with us.","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Down-payment plus emi","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"RAMAMOHAN","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What should I do? the technicians not able to understand Amazon refund process for missing installation parts based on their installation report","answer":"Replace the item","votes":"0","username":"Puneet Takkar","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the warranty gets void if installed by third party?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Puneet Takkar","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which stablizer should be purchased for this AC?","answer":"V-Guard ARI-ZOR 4150 Voltage Stabilizer for Inverter AC Upto 1.5 TON (White, 150 VAC-280 VAC)","votes":"0","username":"Kumar K","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Auto Start feature available or not?","answer":"Available in MiAIe app, where you can schedule auto start and auto shut down.","votes":"0","username":"Kumar K","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to book the instullation? i have placed an order of this ac, but no insullation is showing","answer":"U can call on customer care number and Book the installation.","votes":"0","username":"Puneet Takkar","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f811cfba6a7877c047e"},"product_asin":"B09R3T1QLW","QAs":[{"question":"What all parts will i get in the unit boxes?","answer":"Indoor and outdoor units","votes":"0","username":"Shripad K","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f811cfba6a7877c0481"},"product_asin":"B09TJBPHZR","QAs":[{"question":"What about PCB warranty,  outdoor unit warranty","answer":"1 year comprehensive warranty. After that 4 year pcb warranty and 10 years Compressor warranty","votes":"0","username":"Sun Enterprise Vadodara","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f831cfba6a7877c049c"},"product_asin":"B09R3S2NG6","QAs":[{"question":"Is it suitable for hall with out having AC curtain on Entry gate to kitchen.","answer":"Depends on your room size, otherwise there is no problem, you might have to share some cooking smells with the people in the drawing room","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Shahani","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"ECO friendly kya hai","answer":"Gas eco friendly hai jisse ozone depletion kam hota hai","votes":"0","username":"Prateekk","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling capacity of 5star model??","answer":"This 2 Ton capacity 5 star airconditioner is cooling large hall of 250 to 300 square feet.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Padhye","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"is wifi option available in auto convertable+ 2022","answer":"Yes, it is Wi-Fi enabled and connect to home Wifi network. I have connected with Amazon Alexa and Google. I give voice commands to Alexa to Turn on or off, set the temperature. MirAle software in mobile play store apps can control the airconditioner from anywhere using internet network.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Padhye","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"For exchange do i have to remove old ac","answer":"Yes, we have to keep old airconditioner unit removed by our own technician at our cost. The old unit is picked up while delivering the new airconditioner.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Padhye","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I invoke the manufacturer  warranty? I purchased two units a couple of weeks ago. One of them is making a lot of noise.","answer":"We have to call Panasonic customer care number and provide purchase details. We have to provide Amazon purchase invoice, which can be downloaded from Amazon application. Panasonic technician will visit and resolve the issue.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Padhye","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if I want the copper tube length longer as the location requires?","answer":"Ten feet (3 meter) copper pipe is provided free of cost. As per requirement, additional pipeline is provided and it will be billed as per Panasonic terms and conditions. Panasonic provides cost details for copper pipe, drainage pipe and electricity wiring and installation charges for the additional lines.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Padhye","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Customers who bought 2 ton Panasonic having any complaints?","answer":"Poor customer service.","votes":"0","username":"Prem Sundar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model's remote work on the 2019 model?","answer":"don't know but it should, I guess","votes":"0","username":"Jagdeep","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to know that wether a two ton ac of panasonic has display on the ac and light in the remote. please guide immediately","answer":"Yes Display is in the AC.","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj K Chaurasia","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit base bush support is missing? For otherbrand AC it is available,why it didn't come with outdoor unit?","answer":"Mine is also missing","votes":"0","username":"Prateekk","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to make sure its a 2 ton ac?","answer":"Check details it mention","votes":"0","username":"sabir","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What accessories should the company provide along with  the ac from amazon","answer":"Only copper pipe no wire","votes":"0","username":"sabir","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What us the Max and min temperature that can be set?","answer":"The A/C is good. But do not buy from Amazon. The seller is fraud. They sent the A/C with out the accessories (costing around Rs 3,000). Please read reviews - you will see that it is their standard practice . Even with multiple follow ups, Amazon also did not help. It is a cheating racket. Do not fall for it. Good Luck","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper pipe provided with package ?","answer":"Yes it's copper","votes":"0","username":"Dr Kanhaiah M","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the outdoor unit comes with stand","answer":"The stand to mount the out door unit has to be purchased separately.","votes":"0","username":"MM","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"all pipe are available in the box?","answer":"no pipes in box","votes":"0","username":"Praveen Jain","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require stablizer","answer":"Technically doesn’t require one, but would advise adding an external one for better protection","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it  Hot and cool or for cooling ?","answer":"Only cooling","votes":"0","username":"Soumit B.","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tell me warranty on pcb & compressor","answer":"Pcb 5 year and 10 years for compressor.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a wifi enabled ac?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vibhu Garg","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model with solar panels","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vibhu Garg","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya isme solar panels sath hai","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Dr Kanhaiah M","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 4 way or 2 way","answer":"Vertical automatic but horizontal manual","votes":"0","username":"Dr Kanhaiah M","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Horizontal and vertical swing? Backlit remote?","answer":"Vertical and black light remote display","votes":"0","username":"Soumit B.","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a warmer cum cool ac","answer":"Not for warming.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have both horizontal and veritical swing?","answer":"Only vertical swing.","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC have a 4 direction swing function?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have heater also Hot and cold AC?","answer":"Only Cooling","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"360 degree swing or two side only ?","answer":"2 sides only","votes":"0","username":"Manoj Gokhale…","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 2022 model?","answer":"Yes, it is.","votes":"0","username":"Dr Kanhaiah M","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are we expecting this model to be listed for sale, soon?","answer":"It's 2022 model.","votes":"0","username":"Dr Kanhaiah M","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the product packaged as one single box? Or indoor and outdoor unit will be seperately dispatched?","answer":"There will be two separate boxes for Indoor and Outdoor units.","votes":"0","username":"HEMKANT B.","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is bldc motor used on it?","answer":"No details mentioned","votes":"0","username":"sabir","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f831cfba6a7877c04ad"},"product_asin":"B09RP38FBT","QAs":[{"question":"Is it 2022 model or 2021?","answer":"2022 as it's already mentioned in product name","votes":"0","username":"Ajit Kadam","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is if sufficient for 288 square feet room","answer":"No, it can't be used for that big size, max could be 180 sq","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Box me coper pipe aati he","answer":"Yep, there is a copper pipe upto 10 feet","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2 way or 4 way swing?","answer":"It's a 4 way","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have 3 mt. Copper wire?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 years pcb warranty available or not with this model.?  if yes how to claim 5year pcb warranty.","answer":"Call service center","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac has stand for compressor ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the warranty of the PCB (5 years) valid for the outdoor unit o only for the indoor","answer":"Outdoor","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pls advise how can i get 4 years extended warranty on this product","answer":"Buy extended warranty like go warranty","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"5% cash back on amazone icici credit card means give the exampal","answer":"Read the t&c","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it hve dehumidifire?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the 2020 model also have all the features as 2022 specifically the smart feature i.e. wi-fi compatible with alexa?","answer":"Yess","votes":"0","username":"Salman K.","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does F mean at the end of model number ?","answer":"It refers to flexible connecting","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is pbc warranty","answer":"It's PCB and the warranty is for 5 years","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the wareenty","answer":"10 Years and 5 years","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any warranty on gas charging?","answer":"NA","votes":"0","username":"Anand Tiwary","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f861cfba6a7877c04ea"},"product_asin":"B09RPFQ8Z5","QAs":[{"question":"Stabilizer required for this AC ?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"N S","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it piston compressor","answer":"Sorry I don't have any idea. All I know is, it jas got a good compressor that works well to cool my master bedroom pretty quickly. I have another panasonic a/c of similar type which I bought 1.5 years back, still cools the room well. So, it does the job and durable.","votes":"0","username":"MICHAEL IRUDAYA RAJ","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can we use four way swing in this AC","answer":"160 degree swing only","votes":"0","username":"N S","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its Cooling capacity in watts","answer":"1500w","votes":"0","username":"N S","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Instalments me lena hai","answer":"Yes,you can take in installment","votes":"0","username":"Swati kant","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the installation free?","answer":"499+gst","votes":"0","username":"MICHAEL IRUDAYA RAJ","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is installation charges","answer":"₹500","votes":"0","username":"N S","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Instalation charges","answer":"₹500 in NCR","votes":"0","username":"N S","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"After sales service of this product","answer":"Same like any brand.","votes":"0","username":"MICHAEL IRUDAYA RAJ","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it inverter ac?","answer":"No. Inverter Air conditioners are only available in split AC unit models. They are not available in window models. Also, given the bare existence and low preference for the window models, it is highly unlikely that there would be any possible line of window inverter ACs anytime soon.","votes":"-1","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the size of the box in which the AC is supplied? I need to know if the box can fit in my car.","answer":"Only in SUV","votes":"0","username":"RAJA","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is GST invoice available for this product","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RAJA","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need a GST bill","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RAJA","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter ac?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RAJA","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f861cfba6a7877c04f5"},"product_asin":"B09R4DDVQV","QAs":[{"question":"Is installation included in the price  ?","answer":"No installation and extra wires charges extra","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation including in the price  ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Gupta","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation enclude the price?","answer":"No, we have to pay installation charges extra","votes":"0","username":"Aayush","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do u provide copper pipe & other related cord with ac","answer":"Yes 10 ft copper pipe provide","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Gupta","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are supporting brackets for outdoor unit included in the price","answer":"No, this is charged extra at time of installation","votes":"0","username":"Gadget Guru","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"It require stabilizer as it claims to be Stabilizer Free Operation ?","answer":"Using without stabilizer, seems fine","votes":"0","username":"Gadget Guru","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling and heating both are reqd in ac","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Gupta","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f891cfba6a7877c0548"},"product_asin":"B09RK911MP","QAs":[{"question":"Can Hot and cold both options available in it","answer":"No, but it is a great AC","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh Kaushal","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f8a1cfba6a7877c055c"},"product_asin":"B09ZB69182","QAs":[{"question":"Does it include installation","answer":"No, installation charges extra.","votes":"0","username":"abhi garg","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much carpet area it will cover","answer":"12x14 should be okay if placed at a height of 7-8ft.","votes":"0","username":"Shamik Chanda","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free or chargeable, or it is to be done by the buyer","answer":"By the buyer.","votes":"0","username":"Shamik Chanda","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper connecting pipe and wire included with the AC ?","answer":"Included by mine was defective, had to spend extra on those.","votes":"0","username":"Shamik Chanda","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f8e1cfba6a7877c05ab"},"product_asin":"B09SD9RX33","QAs":[{"question":"Is it with invertor or Non invertor","answer":"Non inverter","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is extra installation charges","answer":"Yes ..3000k","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free or charged??","answer":"Charged 3000","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this copper or aluminium","answer":"Copper","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it an inverter ac?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ABHISHEK MONDAL","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac aaja ne ke baad fiting service kab milegi our vo free hogi ke  charjebal hogi","answer":"Next day but chargeable","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fiting ko service free he","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation and bracket free ?","answer":"Bucket chargeable","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How will installation be done","answer":"Technician will attend","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f901cfba6a7877c05cc"},"product_asin":"B09WDTYJ54","QAs":[{"question":"Free Installation included ?","answer":"No it's chargeable basis.","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"This products installation free or chargeble?","answer":"Product installation is chargeable by Hitachi","votes":"0","username":"Nirav Madariya","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation mandatory from Hitachi?","answer":"Not mandatory","votes":"0","username":"Shreya Gohil","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Room size Kitna cover korega","answer":"120 sq ft","votes":"0","username":"Shreya Gohil","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get Warranty card?","answer":"After installation warranty started for standard one year. Bill copy or installation certificate will be applicable for claiming the warranty.","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Free Installation is included?","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Nirav Madariya","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges","answer":"Around 4500-5000","votes":"0","username":"Vitrag Sheladia","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"1. What is the installation charge? 2. Will the stand and nut/bolts be provided along with the AC unit?","answer":"Stand and nut bolts will be provided by installer with extra charge. Total 2900 /- with stand , white cement, 3 pin plug and services","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model stabilizer free","answer":"No..you have to buy stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation time","answer":"3-4 hours","votes":"0","username":"Vitrag Sheladia","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free or not?","answer":"As per brand policy","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which gas used in this ac ?","answer":"R32","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the PCB warranty period?","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"Vishnu En","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Room size 130 square feet it is suitable ?","answer":"This ac was perfectly matched in 1000 sq feet. Additional 300 sq feet is not bad.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on compressor","answer":"10 Years warranty on Compressor","votes":"0","username":"Vishnu En","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is installation charge? and can be  Install same day of delivery?","answer":"Same day or next day as per your convenience","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"When installing will be done and how","answer":"On 5 th may 2022","votes":"0","username":"Nisarg Parekh","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is single inverter or dual inverter?","answer":"Single","votes":"0","username":"Piyush Agarwal","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is installation charges","answer":"1186","votes":"0","username":"Nisarg Parekh","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many years indoor & outdoor pcv warranty","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"Nisarg Parekh","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Horizontal & Vertical air swing work?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nisarg Parekh","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation included in the price? If yes how do we get the installation done.","answer":"Installation Charges are Extra as Per Company Policy","votes":"0","username":"Vishnu En","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many year of compressor warranty","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"Santanu G.","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about Installation?","answer":"Service not good my advice purchase from marjet","votes":"0","username":"harjinder singh sachdev","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"It’s with free installation","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"harjinder singh sachdev","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation  charges","answer":"1500 + Copper wire 4000 ,so purchase from market where you find cheap from AMAZON","votes":"0","username":"harjinder singh sachdev","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Has it auto cut off featurr?","answer":"Yes off course it is automatic cut off.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f901cfba6a7877c05eb"},"product_asin":"B08Z47LWL4","QAs":[{"question":"What is difference between models 2021 & 2022","answer":"I found nothing except price hike....","votes":"0","username":"ARGHADIP BANERJEE","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which gase is fild in model rsrg518heea/2021in1.5 ton","answer":"Don’t buy online. Neither Amazon nor Hitachi helps in case of warranty issues. I got delivered a defective piece and now none of them are replacing.","votes":"0","username":"Girish Amesara","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many services are free","answer":"Three","votes":"0","username":"ARGHADIP BANERJEE","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya out door unit ke sath stand hai?","answer":"no you have to buy from outside","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation  free?","answer":"no, you have to pay","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this hot & cold a.c","answer":"No colling only","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the difference between 2021 and 2022 model","answer":"rating","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much warranty on pcb nd compressor","answer":"5 year compressor and 10 year PCB","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charge kitna hoga","answer":"Around Rs.1000","votes":"0","username":"Suryamani Singh","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can u please confirm that can i connect this Ac to Hitachi air cloud home app for controlling the ac wirelessly","answer":"No. It does not allow","votes":"0","username":"Sampad Kumar Maity","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has heating mode if have give me steps of how to do heating mode in hitachi 1.5 5 star inverter ac 2021 model","answer":"No there is no heating mode because it is not all weather AC.","votes":"0","username":"Girish Chandra Gautam","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac warranty?","answer":"1 year product, 5 year compressor 10 year PCB","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation charges?","answer":"750 on my time March 2022","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"which model is best 2021 or 2022? why i dont see install option for 2022?","answer":"I would suggest take any other ac hitachi ac is waste of money","votes":"0","username":"Gurpreet Singh","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to create installation request ?","answer":"Please call to customer care no which available with hitachi booklet or use googelThen they will lock your call and do installation within 24-72 hourWhile talking with customer care please keep your bill copy with yousee less","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How the ac will be installed?","answer":"Hitachi guys train for that they will install properly","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this ac work as heater as well in winter? In description it's not mentioned anywhere.","answer":"No you need to take another model for same","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is warranty on PCB?","answer":"Mention in booklet","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a hot and cold AC?","answer":"Cold only","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charge free or not.","answer":"Installation charge is not free. be careful, The Serveice engineer can ask for any amount for installation. So better visit the official website and check for the installation charge. I had to struggle a lot and send 3-4 escalation mail to Hitachi Support to settle with proper amount to be paid for installation.,","votes":"0","username":"Pravin","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"copper cable provided yes or no ?","answer":"Yes but never purchase this product it doesn't provide sufficient colling","votes":"0","username":"Mayank mahajan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it sufficiant for 180 sq ft room on 1st floor? roof is not shaded.","answer":"I think it is","votes":"0","username":"ARGHADIP BANERJEE","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do installation service free in pin 713216","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mayank mahajan","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on Condenser .?","answer":"Worst product please don't but try to avoid this model","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Kumar J D","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"whether hitachi split AC 5 star heating and cooling?","answer":"No, slight warm air u will get if u put ac in 31","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Kumar J D","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Recently i have installed this ac but it is having a water leakage problem.water is leaking from the side and not from the drain pipe. What to do now?","answer":"That water outlet pipe is going to need stright path only, Slightly bend is an water leakage problem is normal.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between rgrs518heea and cgrs518heea and egrs518heea","answer":"All r same","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Kumar J D","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many free service provide by company?","answer":"3 servicing  per 3 months","votes":"0","username":"Suryamani Singh","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac kay sath stabilizer v mile ga","answer":"No stabiliser","votes":"0","username":"Shailesh Singh Bhadauria","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"In case of replacement, who will pay for the  2nd time installation?","answer":"Amazon has to pay","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Kumar J D","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Chinese maid?","answer":"No it’s Japanese company","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kitne maheene ki kist hai","answer":"I have buy with full payment","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have anti corrosion coating?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Kumar J D","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to on Expandable inverter mode","answer":"It’s automatic when required","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have received ac with a small connecting wire. there is no plug. how do i start.","answer":"You need to purchase","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"this model how many warrenty in compressor?","answer":"10 year","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we have any mobile app to control this AC?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation free in Delhi?","answer":"No its paid","votes":"0","username":"Prince Bansal","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f921cfba6a7877c05fc"},"product_asin":"B09SDDT77Y","QAs":[{"question":"manufacture year","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"It s copper condensor","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is full copar","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Digress it have 4 way sir swing feature?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its 2022 model ya 2021","answer":"22","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 5 star ac.","answer":"3 star","votes":"0","username":"FAIR PRICE SHOPPE","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require stablizer?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Vishnu En","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges are included?","answer":"no. charges are not included.","votes":"0","username":"BRAND BUY","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f921cfba6a7877c0604"},"product_asin":"B08H7X6W8P","QAs":[{"question":"Is this model noise free operation??","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Balaji","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f931cfba6a7877c061e"},"product_asin":"B09WDSTF8T","QAs":[{"question":"What about warranty on pcb & compressor?","answer":"Pcb 5 Years and compressor 10 years","votes":"0","username":"mustak khan","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 100 percent copper condenser indoor and outdoor","answer":"Yes absolutely","votes":"0","username":"mustak khan","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which gas has been used . R32 ?","answer":"R42","votes":"0","username":"Tyson_Mike","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why outdoor unit noise very high, looks like a portable generator runing in my roof","answer":"Outdoor unit noise is much higher than usual and other brands...if you think about buying Hitachi....my strict advice is to not buy Hitachi at any cost....I already suffered by this too much....even support also not better...please, you must ho with ither brands.","votes":"0","username":"sumit sharma","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"why 2022 model is cheaper than 2021 model","answer":"It's not cheaper it's companh agenda to build their lost repo","votes":"0","username":"sumit sharma","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this includes mounting angles","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"sumit sharma","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does Copper pipe inclusive in it ? Length of Copper pipe ? installation charges?","answer":"3mtr copper pipe is including, Installation charges please ask amazon customer care.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have turbo mode","answer":"Turbo mode not available in this model.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How soon can this unit be installed after delivery?","answer":"Normally within 24hours, mostly they do it within few hours of delivery.","votes":"0","username":"siva","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a PCB warrenty?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Satish","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f931cfba6a7877c0627"},"product_asin":"B08KWF94JG","QAs":[{"question":"Pcb  warranty?","answer":"1 year comprehensive warranty","votes":"0","username":"Sun Enterprise Vadodara","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer model and rating recommendation for hitachi inverter AC","answer":"Generally not require","votes":"0","username":"Sun Enterprise Vadodara","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f941cfba6a7877c0651"},"product_asin":"B09R4RTJ2B","QAs":[{"question":"What room size is required ?","answer":"400 sq ft it will work well","votes":"0","username":"Navendu Mathur","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot & cold duel compressor?","answer":"Cold only","votes":"0","username":"Navendu Mathur","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Stabilizer required?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Navendu Mathur","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f951cfba6a7877c066a"},"product_asin":"B08Y8Z3PLL","QAs":[{"question":"Is it work in winter for warm room ?","answer":"pls do not buy from amazon","votes":"0","username":"Vg","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether pick up person will uninstall the old AC. If so any charges","answer":"Normally they will not, but you can always work out a deal by offering to pay for it.","votes":"0","username":"Tapas Sen","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this convertible AC?","answer":"I don't know what you mean by 'convertible', but I presume you're asking about it changing its capacity from 1 ton to 1.5 etc. as claimed by some AC advertisements. If that's what you're asking, the answer is no, it is not.","votes":"0","username":"Tapas Sen","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"This model have ambience light  functions ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"NILESH R VEKARIYA","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a warranty on remote? I bought the ac last month and the remote just stopped working. Is there a way to get it replaced?","answer":"Yes contact the customer care","votes":"0","username":"NILESH R VEKARIYA","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many charges for stand and core cutting?","answer":"900","votes":"0","username":"NILESH R VEKARIYA","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ideal for 130 qfeth ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"NILESH R VEKARIYA","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer is necessary","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"NILESH R VEKARIYA","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f951cfba6a7877c066e"},"product_asin":"B07QMBVPGY","QAs":[{"question":"What is the ambient temperature?","answer":"It depends on where you are. Normally setting a temperature between 25-27 degrees is considered ambient","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warrenty on compressor","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is no display then how to check temperature","answer":"Remote has display which will showcase the Temperature you have set.","votes":"0","username":"Ahmed","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f951cfba6a7877c0687"},"product_asin":"B09R4SF5SP","QAs":[{"question":"Electric conjumtion per hour","answer":"Approximately 1unit","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much exactly unit consumption per hour?? Can someone please tell","answer":"Depends on your temp you set up, room conditions etc.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the 0.8 ton 2022 model have a temperature screen?","answer":"Not on the body of the Indoor unit. That only has some LEDs for Power Timer Etc. Temperature can only be seen on the Remote.","votes":"0","username":"Pr0xy","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Company pipe in a box??","answer":"Yes however that does not suffice...also installation guys don't prefer connecting it mentioning it sill caused short circuit if se extend same either another pipe.","votes":"0","username":"Sachina pradhan","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have cancelled my order but no update shown in this regards","answer":"Contact amazon coustomer care, surely they will help you out.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"without GST","answer":"With gst","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has black coating for copper like LG, panosonic??.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is fixed speed?","answer":"Even I am unable to understand what actually that stuff is, but I am using this AC , you can control as you want . It is just a wonderful air conditioner . If you going to purchase, just go for it without any hesitation but don’t forget to purchase stabiliser as well as power plug for long Duration of AC","votes":"0","username":"Anshul Singh Lodhi","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it has autocut sensor ?","answer":"Yes it has , if light fluctuate then you do not have to worry because it is auto stabilising","votes":"0","username":"Anshul Singh Lodhi","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What you mean by fixed speed?","answer":"Non inverter type","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is fixed speed in this ac","answer":"Compressor unit","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Split ac के installation charges  कितने हैं","answer":"1500","votes":"0","username":"Anshul Singh Lodhi","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you install it in rajarhat?","answer":"Ya","votes":"0","username":"Manas D.","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to set automatic off in remote???","answer":"You can use sleep mode or timer option is also available.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does it means by fixed speed??","answer":"Unlike inverter compressor where speed of the compressor varies accordingly. Fixed speed compressor keep running with fixed speed and shut off when room reaches the set temperature.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"As per description by company , nothing mentioned like stabilizer free  0.8 model so does it  need a stabilizer  ?","answer":"Its totally your wish, if you have stable power in your area where there is no fluctuations you can use it with out stabilizer. Inbuilt stabilizer is available. However company's recommend to use one. My all the ac are running without stabilizer without any problem.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are any other charges required at the time of installation?","answer":"Apart from instalation you might be charged for extra length of copper pipe if required. And you might have to pay for wall mount stand for external unit if required. And a 15amp socket which is not included.","votes":"0","username":"Nadeem Ahamed Baji","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have stabiliser free operation?","answer":"Yes.... Stabilser needed if in your place electric fluctuation is more.","votes":"0","username":"HP","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Without disply screen how to manage temperature ?","answer":"The remote shows the temperature. You can use that.","votes":"0","username":"Fahad A.","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to see temperacture if dont have disply in ac","answer":"Uuss the AC Remote. The remote has temperature display","votes":"0","username":"Fahad A.","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are the switches on remote visible in dark. Is there any backlight?","answer":"No backlight, but the buttons are visible in dark.","votes":"0","username":"Fahad A.","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Doesn’t have temperature display in indoor unit ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ravi Nagpal","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it returnable product if it was not useful or other problem","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ravi Nagpal","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation charge as of june 2022, as per your statement, @₹701 +gst till 31st may 2022 already ended?","answer":"I paid 1300 rupees for installation. What mentioned here as 701+taxes is wrong","votes":"0","username":"Shaik Thouhid Hussain","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer required or not??","answer":"It depends upon supply voltage.","votes":"0","username":"Ravi Nagpal","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model tv or uv series?","answer":"This is a 0.8 ton split AC.","votes":"0","username":"Simanchala Panda","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the size of its outdoor unit","answer":"Normal size, light, copper condenser and strong.","votes":"0","username":"Simanchala Panda","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they have service provider in NCR region  for afterwards service ?","answer":"Must be. It’s the company of high repute.","votes":"0","username":"Simanchala Panda","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb price ?","answer":"Not aware.","votes":"0","username":"Simanchala Panda","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Minimum temperature???","answer":"Have not checked but my drawing room gets ambient in a relatively short time.","votes":"0","username":"Simanchala Panda","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f961cfba6a7877c06b4"},"product_asin":"B09SW6XS13","QAs":[{"question":"Is it all weather split AC?","answer":"YES SIR","votes":"0","username":"BEST ELECTRONICS FOR YOU","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a 2022 model?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Charge installation cost proper say","answer":"1500","votes":"0","username":"BEST ELECTRONICS FOR YOU","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this available for free installation","answer":"Chargeable Installation","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it full copper or aluminum","answer":"Copper","votes":"0","username":"Sabyasachi","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Final price with installation  and copper piping?","answer":"I had to pay for 2 mtrs of extra piping at 330/mtr. Installation was around 800 incl tax and stand was 750 additional","votes":"0","username":"Sabyasachi","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model have both Hot & Cold air options ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sabyasachi","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f971cfba6a7877c06ce"},"product_asin":"B09SW8FP11","QAs":[{"question":"Is this model indor unit is smaller than other brand 5 star indor unit?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"satya deep","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote ma dew clean ka button nahi deya hi.it is a old model","answer":"Don't buy, I have returned the AC on 04/06/2022 as it was faulty, and still Amazon not refunded my paid amount.","votes":"0","username":"rupan das","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any free service ??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"satya deep","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"My room area is 168sq ft but room indoor temperature doesn't go below 25 C. What is problem in my unit ?","answer":"Don't buy, it's defective item.","votes":"0","username":"rupan das","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I already have stabilizer which is from 130v to 280v will this be needed with this ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there outdoor wall stand in box ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product come with kit ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Aalok Singh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product come with kit ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Room temperature not going below 28, is it normal?","answer":"My room temp reaches 19c, look for additional settings","votes":"0","username":"SRINIVASA R.","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have any coating on condenser like blue fin?","answer":"Yes, it has coating","votes":"0","username":"Harshal M.","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I live on sixth floor and internal piping is done by builder they have given 3 core wire. Can i run this ac with 3 core wire instead of 4 core?","answer":"Yes it is run on 3 wires","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Daikin ka Air conditioner non inverter","answer":"Inverter hai","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want indoor unit only","answer":"Contact the customer care","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long air flow?","answer":"About 10 to 12 feet","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it sutable for 15*18 feet","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any anti corrosion coating on the coils for the condenser and indoor blower units?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"abhiraj","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this model has a rottary compressor  or a swing compressor?","answer":"swing compressor","votes":"0","username":"M khan","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have anti corrosion coating on its indoor and outdoor units?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"abhiraj","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Indoor me Temperature nahi dikhai deta ha","answer":"Dikhta hai... Room ka temperature aur cooling temperature dono dikhatr hai","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is a convertable AC","answer":"convertible AC","votes":"0","username":"S.R","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it come with copper coil indoor as well as outdoor?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"S.R","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much of covered aria","answer":"110 to 160","votes":"0","username":"S.R","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it wi fi facility","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I dont want installation can I only buy the ac","answer":"No, installtion should be done by company only","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has streamer discharge technology ???","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i control with mobile","answer":"You can but by mobile with IR blaster, no wifi","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference between mtkm50u & ftkm50u","answer":"FTKM50. is a better model","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"When it will available","answer":"depend on Supply & demand ratio","votes":"0","username":"S.R","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any exchange offer","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"S.R","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"4way swing is there","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it do hot and cold both ?","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference between ftkm50 & mtkm50u?","answer":"Nothing","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is Hot & cold?","answer":"Only cold","votes":"0","username":"Vikash","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between ftkm50u and mtkm50u models ?","answer":"Not much... Just same","votes":"0","username":"Dhiraj Parmar","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between mtkm50u and ftkm50u?","answer":"None","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC requires Stabilizer ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it dual split invertor","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this inverter ac or non inverter?","answer":"Invertor","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have 4 way swing?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a Copper wire","answer":"Yes 3 metre","votes":"0","username":"Vasudevan","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it requires stablizer.","answer":"Yes , protects equipment from power fluctuations.","votes":"0","username":"Ahmed","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation done by my self?","answer":"Installation done company service agent","votes":"0","username":"Vasudevan","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does AC Remote have backlight?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I need to install stabiliser separately?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vasudevan","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"4 way swing or two way","answer":"2 way","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2022 model?","answer":"please check the BEE energy label image, it will say if its 2022 or 2021. The 2022 modely consumes almost 40-50 units lesser than the 2021 model. Around 787 units. This link now has both the 2021 and 2022 models option, so click on 2022 which will be about 4k costlier than 2021 model.","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any other charges applicable for purchasing compressor fitting bracket?","answer":"yes, 1500 for the installations and they will bring outdoor unit stand for which additional charge will be there. If you buy from online generally the installations guys are not very happy and will be grumbling :)","votes":"1","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the PCB warranty?","answer":"It’s 5 years.","votes":"0","username":"Sasidhar Reddy","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will  GST shown separately  in invoice","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power consumption in watt","answer":"power consumption in watts is difficult as being an inverter ac it will fluctuate. Unlike traditional ac that is either on or off stage; Inverter ac generally start at a low wattage and then increase to maximum till the room reaches the desired temparature and it will then reduce the power and go to maintaining the cooling level. So throughout the time you keep an ac on, it will be doing this. You can only measure using kwh or units and generally I have noticed for an 8 hours of running in a 200 sq.ft room at night its about 4 units.see less","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please inform unit consuption per year in 3 star and 5 star rating?","answer":"do check the energy label attached to know the exact units and divide it by 1600 hours, that will give you the hourly unit consumption when its running. ( they assume we will normally use the ac only for 200 days out of the 365 days a year for 8 hours each)","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"copper pipe is included in Box. if yes how much size do they send in box?","answer":"the length of the copper tube is mentioned in the specification and it will be there in the box. If you need extra piping the installation guys will need to be informed.","votes":"0","username":"chakky","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the minimum power consumption in economo mode?","answer":"Max 1.5 units per day at 27 degree with power save mode","votes":"0","username":"SRINIVASA R.","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"It has temperature display","answer":"no. Just on the remote","votes":"0","username":"Prateek Agarwal","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty on outdoor unit","answer":"5 Years","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Comprehensive warranty of how many years?","answer":"1 Year","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there Stabilizer inside ??","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Indoor ke sath kina metar wayer milta hai","answer":"10 meter","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the load for ac in kw (not unit consumption), about kw load like 1kw or 2kw load","answer":"2 kw","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Kumar Gupta","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9a1cfba6a7877c0721"},"product_asin":"B09R9RDNNH","QAs":[{"question":"Can we install the product with our local installation team","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"whether Temperature diplay is available on the Main unit display","answer":"No, only on remote","votes":"0","username":"Anonymous","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it convertible or not?","answer":"No, just an inverter AC","votes":"0","username":"Anonymous","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has Conda Airflow ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anonymous","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hot and cold ac ?","answer":"Not worth please dont buy","votes":"0","username":"Gupta general store","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold ac?","answer":"Cold","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it having dew clean technology","answer":"Yes but I don't know how to use","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac wifi working","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any installation price to be given?","answer":"Nearly 2200rs","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mera invoice bill kho gaya hai exact date bhi yaad nhi service kaise karaye","answer":"Download from Amazon app","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the old AC be exchanged?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if i install the product with a person other than company technician? Will i get the warranty benefits still?","answer":"No your warranty will be gone","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power consumption per hr howmuch units","answer":"No odea","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"10 feet pipe ata h","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this have wifi functionality and if not where can i get the wifi optional kit??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ramiz","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9a1cfba6a7877c0726"},"product_asin":"B09R4RVTMT","QAs":[{"question":"Coverage area of this ac ?","answer":"Coverage OK for a hall of capacity 32 square metres.","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9b1cfba6a7877c0732"},"product_asin":"B09R4RZB11","QAs":[{"question":"I want gst invoice","answer":"While buying it you can select with gst and then they will provide you that.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mtkl50u or atkl50uv16 which one better?","answer":"MTKL50U is 4 star and it’s the best model. In fact the light bill has been very very reasonable.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many services are free with AC ?","answer":"For me it is TWO. Don’t know now.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. T.R. Kesavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Material copper hai","answer":"Yes it’s pure copper. Direct from the company.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"is thre any charger for instalation","answer":"Yes there are installation charges. Approx ₹7000 to ₹10,000 as it all depends on the copper and then wiring and also mccb if needed","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"PCB warranty","answer":"PCB warrant is for 5 years.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the price include installation charges?","answer":"No installation is extra.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Connecting wire available in box or not","answer":"All r excluded.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is not available in our area.who is going to install.. waht about the Service after Installation.please clear","answer":"Initially when bought the got a call from several Daikin people. You would need to visit the Daikin website India and then get in touch with them.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much is the installation cost","answer":"₹7000 to ₹15000. Depends on the wiring mccb copper if need.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"In case of exchange, will they uninstall the exiting unit or should it be already uninstalled?","answer":"Yes. Otherwise charges r applicable.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold option availabe in any season","answer":"Hot & cold is marketing stunt.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does installation kit contain? What is Length of copper wire and drainage pipe comes with package is?","answer":"Indoor Unit, Outdoor Unit, Remote Control, User manual, Warranty Card & Standard Installation Kit","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require Stabiliser","answer":"Stabilizers required where power supply fluctuates","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this fot 175 sq feet area room size?","answer":"Yes you can. It's powerful.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are ftkl50 and ftkt50 model are same specification","answer":"It's better to go with 2022 Models.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is  to reset setting post powercut","answer":"Nope. It's only reset the settings.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why no response after purchase through Amazon????","answer":"Try to send the email directly to Daikin company with the Amazon reference. It would help.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this product you can give a copper pipe or not","answer":"Yes copper pipe comes in the kit. But it's limited.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to avail 5% cash back on hdfc millinia credit card?","answer":"Before buying check with the bank. And get the complete info. And then move ahead.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"May i get gst tax invoice the the product","answer":"While purchasing you can see that and then buy it.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My roop is 235 sqft sutebal this ac for my room","answer":"Take the guidance of AC selection on Amazon. It will guide you better.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac timer available?","answer":"Oh yes it's available. And it's superb.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about Installation and its expenses","answer":"Keep in mind ₹7000 to ₹15000.","votes":"0","username":"Pavan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dakin sound less ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9c1cfba6a7877c0748"},"product_asin":"B09SW7PK5L","QAs":[{"question":"Installation free or paid on this product","answer":"Paid, they charge 1550","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will pipe be provided for installation along with the AC?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which one is best 4star or 5 star?","answer":"4star","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to coordinate with Daikin for installation?","answer":"We ll do it","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9c1cfba6a7877c0758"},"product_asin":"B09R4QLDWK","QAs":[{"question":"are 1.5 ton 3 star  fixed speed","answer":"Don't buy it's waste","votes":"0","username":"syed R.","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the manufacturing year of this ac","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"installation in whose scope ?","answer":"Installation is in customer scope and Daikin representative charges more than the market rate.","votes":"0","username":"Susmita Naru","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the flaps be controlled to move left, right, up and down ?","answer":"It can move up and down new models have left and right too","votes":"0","username":"Nithin kumar","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it model no flt50uv16v3....??","answer":"Yesss","votes":"0","username":"shanmukha","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this daiken ac r hot & cold 3 star","answer":"This is for Summers, cold air excretion","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this hot &cold","answer":"It is only cold","votes":"0","username":"romesh chand kapil","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copperpipe length ?","answer":"3 meter","votes":"0","username":"ELECTRONICS WHOLESALE","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the seller - DawnTech Retail is not giving the copper wire in the product?","answer":"3 meters comes in the box seller don’t need to give it comes from the manufacturer.","votes":"0","username":"Nithin kumar","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can temprature be changed in this ac?","answer":"Temperature display not given in indoor but only given in remote only","votes":"0","username":"sadhiq","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Phone operate option is there","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"sadhiq","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the noise level of indore & outdoor unit","answer":"Noise Level: 38 db(A); Ambient Operation: 50°C","votes":"0","username":"sadhiq","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many wire inside the boxes","answer":"One","votes":"0","username":"Devender","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"gtl50tv16v3 Realease date ?","answer":"Everything is ok but customer care service is very bed.","votes":"0","username":"Ashu kumar","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this an inverter based unit?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SATNAM ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rl50uv16u3 which year model","answer":"2018","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Set temperature high'? And low what?","answer":"35c to 20","votes":"0","username":"prathap","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac has any coating on condenser fins?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"prathap","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can someone recommend a double booster stabilizer model for this A/C?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"prathap","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model no flt50uv16v3...?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"prathap","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9d1cfba6a7877c0763"},"product_asin":"B09SW7RWSD","QAs":[{"question":"How to order. Who will attend for standard installation","answer":"Brand will contact for installation within 24-36 Hrs of delivery. Standard Installation @₹1500 +GST (Additional charges for core drilling, extra copper wire, stand & other accessories will be applicable). Contact brand for further assistance @011-40319300/1860-180-3900","votes":"0","username":"Allied System Works","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit Mounting bracket included in the product or not","answer":"Not included. In my experience other brands also don't give mounting bracket.","votes":"0","username":"Anirban Mukherjee","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there stabilizer inside ?","answer":"Company claims but alwqys better to add exyernal stabilizer ,Bluebird one is good","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Kalra","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9e1cfba6a7877c0786"},"product_asin":"B08BTJL4CT","QAs":[{"question":"Is it 2022 latest model??","answer":"Model does not matter. It is not a car whose resale value will be decided by year of manufacture.","votes":"0","username":"Ranger","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Electricity consumption per hour","answer":"Don’t buy AC if worried about power consumption.","votes":"0","username":"Ranger","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac heavyduty or not?","answer":"Very very very heavy duty.","votes":"0","username":"Ranger","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9e1cfba6a7877c078a"},"product_asin":"B09R4RFRFY","QAs":[{"question":"Including kit or not","answer":"You have to buy stand for the outdoor unit. Rest is in the package itself.","votes":"0","username":"Prateek Agarwal","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"It has wifi","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Prateek Agarwal","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the energy plug comes with the indoor unit or outdoor unit??? The one which we connect to the switch board?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"AMIT NATH","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about exchange offer","answer":"I didn't take it","votes":"0","username":"surinder oberoi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any charges for wall drilling ? And how much for stand ?","answer":"Depends usually it’s an additional cost.","votes":"0","username":"AMIT NATH","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation charge","answer":"1500","votes":"0","username":"Prateek Agarwal","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the outdoor unit placed in closed space","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prateek Agarwal","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper wire included ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"AMIT NATH","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What else is included in the box ? Copper wires, tubes, water ourlet tube ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"surinder oberoi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does copper wire comes with this ac","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"surinder oberoi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need to purchase on my firms name but delivery is at a different addrrss . Is that Ok. And where do i put in the gst details","answer":"Co gst no.","votes":"0","username":"surinder oberoi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a inverter ac?","answer":"yes it is inverter A/C","votes":"0","username":"surinder oberoi","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the remote come with wall mount?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"KANNAN UMESH","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any coating on the outdoor unit to prevent from dust and rust?","answer":"Yes. Anti rust painting done","votes":"0","username":"KANNAN UMESH","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3f9e1cfba6a7877c0795"},"product_asin":"B09R4QY15Z","QAs":[{"question":"My room us 285 sq.ft...is it enough for my room","answer":"Yes its ok","votes":"0","username":"vipul singh","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it advisable for drawing dining hall ?","answer":"Yes 100%.  I have it on my 250 + sq room, works absolutely fine","votes":"0","username":"Soum","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many unit it consume","answer":"That depends on your usage and the temperature at which the cooling is set for","votes":"0","username":"Soum","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stabilizer required","answer":"This depends on your electric supplier, for me it doesn't. CESC does a brilliant job in voltage stabilisation","votes":"0","username":"Soum","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between 2021 and 2022 2.2 ton ac","answer":"It is always preferred to buy the 22 version which is newer in the market. its a generic choice for all products mostly","votes":"0","username":"Soum","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does hot n cold come in 2.2 daikin","answer":"Don't think so, at least the one I bought it doesn't","votes":"0","username":"Soum","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa01cfba6a7877c07d7"},"product_asin":"B09NS54RPJ","QAs":[{"question":"Refrigeration gas how many years","answer":"It depends on your usage","votes":"0","username":"SRI","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Horizental fan movement","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SRI","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have wifi","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it heat the room in the winter season?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is 5in1","answer":"5 in 1 means - AC will work on 100, 80, 60 and 40 percent capacity as per users' choice. Fifth option is high capacity which is 110 percent.","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good idea to buy AC online?","answer":"Compare price in local market also then decide only on the basis of price rest things are same.","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery and installation happens at the same day or different?","answer":"You have to call them for installation and it will be done in 72 hours","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Mishra","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does L.G. provide after sale service  ? If, yes  in how many days??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"BIRENDRA KUMAR CHOURASIYA","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they provide copper wire for installation or we have to buy it ourselves","answer":"Standard length wire provided which will be sufficient. If you have different requirement, you have to pay for extra wire.","votes":"0","username":"Anju","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac need stabilizer","answer":"I'm not using stabilizer. voltage fluctuation is very less in my area.","votes":"0","username":"Anju","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is AC installation included in this price ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much Colling capacity 4600 or 5000 watt?","answer":"4600","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it includes installation?","answer":"No,excluded installation. They will charge you 1199+GST for installation,that amount lumpsump 1.5k Approx.","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is all about after sales services, how can we reach out local for after sales services, please share all details here","answer":"Yes,they have franchise partners,they are authorised,and the technician also authorised by LG TPA.","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is warranty card with stamp included ?","answer":"No stamp but warranty card in box","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the lg technician install stabilizer i bought ??","answer":"Yes with extra cost","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of copper pipe provided by You in  package","answer":"3meter","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Paik","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stablizer required?","answer":"Not needed. I'm not using.","votes":"0","username":"Anju","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is these ac works with alexa","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"Anju","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"10 years on compressor with gas charging warranty. so what does it mean regarding gas warranty?","answer":"Gas charging will be free of cost when required","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"On which side of the ac is power supply wire copper wire","answer":"Right side","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we get 4 way swing in 3star?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sanjib Paul","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require separate stabilizer to be installed??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many times to take chilled the room","answer":"10-15 mins","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many times to chilled the room","answer":"It taakes 2-5 min max. But don't buy this product. No left right swings.","votes":"0","username":"Pradeep","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is intallation included?","answer":"No, you have to pay for it","votes":"0","username":"VK","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"will i get copper pipe with this, is there anything missing in comparison to offline shops","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amitava","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it even 2022 Model?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sanjib Paul","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"copper pipe & wire comes in the box ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sanjib Paul","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Not able to attach any stabilizer","answer":"No","votes":"1","username":"Sanjib Paul","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installed ka paisa dene ka","answer":"Yes Installation charge +gst","votes":"0","username":"Mahfuzul Haque","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have auto restart post power cut?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mahfuzul Haque","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Display page showing pcb waranty it's true","answer":"5 years PCB warranty","votes":"0","username":"Mahfuzul Haque","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it also purify rooms air ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mahfuzul Haque","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's hot and cold Ac","answer":"Cooling is Not bad... but ac indoor unit is not good look..... Very small size unit... not good look... it's shown has local assemble ac look... Local brand ac indoor unit also very good... But LG indoor unit is too bad look... Feel not good....","votes":"0","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much cooling capacity in this ac","answer":"Cooling is ok","votes":"-1","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charge ???","answer":"For installation 1,415 rupees charged and ac outdoor unit stand 895 rupees charged.... But selling in shop's 400 rupees that stand.... why charged double amount LG....","votes":"1","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does Lg provide the stand for fixing outdoor unit","answer":"Provided for Payment cost 895 rupees...","votes":"0","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is installation charge?","answer":"1,415 rupees charged for installation","votes":"0","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have vertical & horizontal swing, both?","answer":"Yes","votes":"-1","username":"Karthik.M","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work in sub zero temperatures?","answer":"Ac did not start after installation..ni pta bhai bekar ac deliver hua mujhe... shameful disgusting","votes":"0","username":"Raunak Singh","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does LG provide free services in the warranty period ?","answer":"Service is not good..my problem have not solved after 2 months...galat item delivere kiya upar se mante b nhi..never  buy online","votes":"0","username":"Raunak Singh","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why AC colling capacity down after 1 year","answer":"Because n to brand or nhi seller guarantee leta h.. ghumate h sb","votes":"0","username":"Raunak Singh","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Open drawing room me 1.5 ton work krega or top floor pe","answer":"Dono jagah","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Mishra","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why length is so less? Same as 1 ton indoor unit.","answer":"Remote control stand not available","votes":"0","username":"Hirendra Kumar","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it all weather ac","answer":"No it's cool only ac","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Tiwary","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 years warranty on pcb . Is this warranty on both the pcbs? Further kindly clarify about the warranty on Gas.","answer":"No warranty on gas leakage, no company gives this","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Tiwary","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if the mrp shown here is different from the mrp on company website for the same model number?","answer":"Your choice, don't buy","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Tiwary","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa11cfba6a7877c07fa"},"product_asin":"B09WV7FRZW","QAs":[{"question":"Is inverter required for AC.","answer":"No, you should run this on aC electricity","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is insurance also available on this AC?","answer":"Yes, you can go for general insurance for household products...","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with a remote hanger because my unit doesn't has one?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Akhil","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Voltage range in which it can function? Want to know if it needs a stablizer.","answer":"230v is mentioned, but I have seen it work in between the range of 215-220 v ,occasionally when voltage gets that low","votes":"0","username":"Akhil","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why the AC switch off automatically after few minutes?","answer":"Normally AC stops compressor when reaches to the desired temperature. If you set 24 and room temperature reaches to 24 then it will stop compressor auto, if it not then you need to talk to the customer care , may be thermostat not working properly..","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jw-q18wuza and tw-q18wuza lg ac difference","answer":"Yes Minor differences","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jw and tw difference","answer":"Jw 2020 series and pw 2022 series","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it work as a heater?","answer":"No, It will not , you can increase the temp, will give you same effect","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this would fit to my last 1.5ton ac slot?","answer":"Yes it will... Still some adjustments required, it has some foam fillings to set that","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do5star come in 4in 1 option because on lg site its showing in 4star","answer":"Yes it is 5Star and is with 4 in 1 settings..","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"alexa or google assistance support this?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the temperature range for this ac? How much low temp can be set?","answer":"16 is the lowest...","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Instalation charges to be paid or not?","answer":"Insttalation charge extra","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"1our electric consumed","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"FAIR PRICE SHOPPE","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"No exchange d product with available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation cost included?","answer":"No it is not included, you need to pay extra 500+ gst","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep Kumar","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there Any harm in ac if i will not use stabilizer","answer":"Well, if you are buying a 40k ac I don't think it should be a problem to buy a decent stabilizer ,considering it would just cost you around 2.5k nowadays,","votes":"0","username":"Akhil","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there Any harm in ac if i will not use stabilizer","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it require stabilizer in low or high temperature","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i purchase spareparts from lg  like psb,motor etc for 1.5  to a.c  5star by on line.?","answer":"Not, officially from lg you can't but","votes":"0","username":"Akhil","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between 4 star & 5star model?","answer":"5 star model convertable wifi model","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats 4 in 1 convertable exact means? Plz explain in details?.","answer":"ac work 4 type according to weather 0.6 ton,1 ton,1.2 ton and 1.5 ton","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model is best old or new","answer":"New, as always","votes":"0","username":"Aradhya.inc","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wi fi enabled or not","answer":"Yes with this model","votes":"0","username":"Aradhya.inc","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it have antibacterial filter?","answer":"Nop but it has pollution filter","votes":"0","username":"Aradhya.inc","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this made in India or Thailand?","answer":"Thailand","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does its copper pipe come with ocean black protection?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it required stabilizer or it works without stabilizer?","answer":"No stabilizer required","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference fraom old model of 2020 vs 2022 model?","answer":"2022 model 4 in 1 convertible","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have manual swing or automatic swing of fins?","answer":"manual swing","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference b/w 2020 and 2022 model ?","answer":"New one is 4-in-1","votes":"0","username":"Aradhya.inc","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i get it installed from outside vendor other than LG ? Will it affect the warranty ?","answer":"No don’t do it. This will void your warranty","votes":"0","username":"BHUDEV","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"installed added its wriiten..","answer":"You will have to pay installation charges extra as charged by the company.","votes":"0","username":"Sunil Kumar","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"GST invoice available hai ya nhi????","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shom","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa11cfba6a7877c0808"},"product_asin":"B09NS5B6TP","QAs":[{"question":"hot and cool model comes in 5star rating","answer":"No, I have 3 star only and as per my knowledge it comes only in 3 star rating till date.","votes":"0","username":"Rohtash","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling have inverter functions to save energy by reducing  capacityDoes Heating mode also have the same?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Irshaan","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this Unit have Wi Fi connectivity","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nitin C.","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Vaccum available in this AC?","answer":"No wifi connectivity in this product.","votes":"0","username":"Gaurav Goel","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stabilizer needed in LG 1.5 ac","answer":"Not required but recomend if frequent voltage fluctuations are there.","votes":"0","username":"Jaspreet","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there too much noise? In the outdoor unit?","answer":"Not at all, this is one of the most quite unit i have used.","votes":"0","username":"Jaspreet","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Many are telling cooling isn’t happening? Is it true? How was your experience?","answer":"NCR current outdoor temperature 42°C AC running at 24°C temperature and room temperature is 26°C. Hope that answers your question. :)","votes":"0","username":"Jaspreet","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is Installation charge added in this amnt","answer":"I was charged additional installation amount.","votes":"0","username":"Jaspreet","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac actually 2022 model because picture of iseer rating shoe 2021 model","answer":"Yes it's 2022 made","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used in winters also?","answer":"Yes sure.","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Kumar Kanaujia","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get the ac installation done by a technician other than the lg service technician?","answer":"No please don't do this otherwise ur warranty void","votes":"0","username":"Salman Irfani","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa11cfba6a7877c0815"},"product_asin":"B09NS5CBC5","QAs":[{"question":"What is angular style","answer":"Its a good but for smaller room. Just like something os better than nothing. It's just around 1.2 ton. Cooling capacity is low than others in that price range. Looks small and decent.","votes":"0","username":"Khaja Sheraz","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compulsory to install from Amazon ? Can’t we get it installed from outside?","answer":"You can install the AC from LG. That is must. If you install from the local technician, then warranty will not be covered. Only LG technician can be able to enter the product serial number and activate the 10 years warranty. Once the AC got delivered you will get the call from LG for installation.","votes":"0","username":"JAMAL","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the installation charges??","answer":"1450","votes":"0","username":"Khaja Sheraz","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to billed at Selhi address at my gst regustered address and installation in ncr. Is it possible to get gst input?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ujjwal utsav","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is angular? which is mentioned in the description","answer":"A few months back I had purchased a ac of LG which are of very good quality.  However the technicians are horrific and fitted the ac at an angle claiming that the water needs to be drained out.  The outflow pipe in the unit itself is at an angle to assist the water flow.","votes":"0","username":"Noel Parras D'Cruz","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its cover 180 sft.?","answer":"Max 110 sqft.","votes":"0","username":"Khaja Sheraz","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation Free?","answer":"No, It is about Rs 1199/- + GST + cost of bracket for external unit. + If they have to drill a slab, drilling through wall is included.","votes":"0","username":"Sharad Patel","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free?","answer":"No around 2150","votes":"0","username":"Mohit S.","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the installation charges","answer":"For split ac installation charges are 1500","votes":"0","username":"ujjwal utsav","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have read many reviews saying that copper wire is missing. What i should do if I find it missing and why it is happening?","answer":"Simple return the order and ask for replacement. Take a video while unpacking the boxes which will be a proof that the copper pipes are missing/stolen by the Delivery guys or at Amazon Warehouse. Amazon customer service will never give full refund of the stolen/missing copper pipes. Keep returning & replacing the order until you get the copper pipes in the box.see less","votes":"0","username":"No Installation service bill f…","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the copper wire/ inter connecting pipe included in the box in 2022 model? I can see customer reviews complaining that they are not included.","answer":"Copper pipes are included inside the Outer unit box of all brands of AC. Delivery guys or Amazon Warehouse steal them cleverly from the sealed Outer unit box. If there are 3 strings of Plastic wire wrapped around the Outer unit box then you might find the Copper pipes inside but if there are only 2 plastic wires, then the copper pipes will surely be missing/stolen. Return the replace the order  until you get the copper pipes. Installation guy will charge you Rs.1120 per Meter and Amazon customer service will give refund only for Rs.750 per meter which is very very unfair.see less","votes":"0","username":"No Installation service bill f…","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much it consumes at 24 degree in 8 hours ,1.5 ton 2 star ac","answer":"3 units","votes":"0","username":"Roy…","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do it require to install stabilizer separately? What will be better as other stabilizer voltage range is lower as mentioned by this ac.","answer":"No need to install a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Roy…","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation pipe are available or not","answer":"Avialable","votes":"0","username":"Raj","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"outdoor noice level in db","answer":"Under 30 dB, I hope","votes":"0","username":"Roy…","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Filter is on top or behind front panel?","answer":"On top","votes":"0","username":"Raj","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the installation be done in a different location?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raj","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on compressor ??","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"nihalkumar","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why this has soo many bad reviews? Is the size of this ac too small to affect cooling and power consumption?","answer":"Power consumption rating was only small difference from 3*, so purchased 2*.Not sure of the reason, but size of indoor units,5* > 4* > 3* > 2* . So 2* actually fitted in a compact wall, where 5* would've been hindered by other objects on wall.I don't see difference in cooling.It is dual inventor, so I expect efficiency gain when left open with few people. Recently purchased, so yet to evaluate.see less","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much to pay for installation?","answer":"1450 for installation and 750 extra for stand","votes":"0","username":"Anand soni","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Length of Inter connecting pipe?","answer":"10ft","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"which is better lg 1 ton 3 star dual inverter split ac model - ps-q12ynxe1, or lg 1 ton 5 star ai dual inverter wi-fi split ac - model - ps-q13swzf, o","answer":"Oviously 5 star will save more energy.. But you need to look at additional cost of purchase vs savings over the lifetym of the product","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much length Inter connecting pipe","answer":"10ft","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Minimum temprature?","answer":"Min. Temprature is 16 and it really cool in 3mins.. awesome feeling","votes":"0","username":"biswaranjan panda","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa31cfba6a7877c083f"},"product_asin":"B07KRBW7X8","QAs":[{"question":"Is it ok for 500 square feet area","answer":"Yes if it is open hall. If rooms are there then it is the matter of ventilation. Just walls are the problems as in my case","votes":"0","username":"Ashok K.","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this chargeable ac","answer":"No it's not chargeable","votes":"0","username":"prashubh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the ac battery powered or with electric cord?","answer":"AC is Electricity powered like all other ACs. It has an Inverter technology based Compressor - it does not run on Battery Inverter. Please be ready to pay big electricity bills whenever you think of installing any AC.","votes":"0","username":"VP2019","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"My room size is 115 sq ft. so 1 or 1.5 ton which will be better for electricity savings point of view?","answer":"1 ton is sufficient if not on top floor or too much solar (sun) gain, else go for higher capacity.","votes":"0","username":"VP2019","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Ac running on inverter or direct electricity connection ?? Pls explain","answer":"Electricity. Inverter is just the Technology name in the compressor.","votes":"0","username":"VP2019","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require a stabiliser or it has a inbuilt stabiliser?","answer":"No stabiliser required. Does not have an inbuilt stabiliser.","votes":"0","username":"VP2019","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any free service with the product?","answer":"3 free service within a year.","votes":"0","username":"MANISH Dixit","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether 1st service is free","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANISH Dixit","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange offer in LG window ac","answer":"It's an average ac it works well when it was new.","votes":"0","username":"prashubh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa51cfba6a7877c0882"},"product_asin":"B09NS59LJV","QAs":[{"question":"does the outdoor fan have Ac motor or DC motor","answer":"B L D C  Motor","votes":"0","username":"M K K","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the actual mrp of this product? this website claims its mrp is rs. 75990 while other websites shows its mrp just rs 61990.","answer":"INR 61,990/-","votes":"0","username":"M K K","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I need to pay for uninstalling exchange AC?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"+sai++","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Would Amazon or seller pay if copper pipe missing in packaging? Has anyone got it paid if so?","answer":"If you find missing anything in original product, return the product.","votes":"0","username":"manoj jadon","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the ac installation charge really around 5-6k ?","answer":"No only 1415 rs","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges","answer":"1415 rs","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does stand and wire is provided or not?","answer":"Wire is provider and stand is extra charge","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is standard installation charges included in the cost or it has to be paid separately to the engineer post installation?","answer":"1415+750(stand)","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether stablizer is required for inverter AC?","answer":"No not required built in","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if I dont go with brand installation and get the ac installed via local person, will that affect the warranty?","answer":"It might affect the warranty. Check with the LG customer care","votes":"0","username":"Vijayendra","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why bajaj EMI option is not available","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"exchange offer ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I install 2 of these AC's on a single phase connection?","answer":"Yes, u can install even 4 on a single phase connection","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Singal","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"when i will use these ac in 24 degree celsius upto 24 hours ??? how much unit will consume ???????","answer":"Almost 12 units when u use it in a closed room.","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Singal","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have Wi-Fi?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Singal","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"3meters copper pipe is missing from both indoor and outdoor unit","answer":"Inter connecting pipes are included in box.and that is fixed by LG Engineers.","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"6 in 1 ac How works auto mode let me know","answer":"There’s a button aligned to it which can be used","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation plates included or we have to buy separately","answer":"स्टँड  चार्जेबल हें","votes":"0","username":"Vijay Ghorpade","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include copper wire or not ?","answer":"Some time dealer put the wire in the box and some time not. I got the copper wire and my friend didn't. Amazon will refund the Copper wire charges @ 950/- per meter upto three meter only producing the job sheet clearly mentioned that coper wire is not received in the box. Don't open the box yourself, authorized representative of the company will open the box.see less","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Bhardwaj","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"My room.size is 12'x12',  will this AC work?","answer":"No. Not that effective.","votes":"0","username":"Milan Garg","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gas charging free for 10 yrs what is the meaning?","answer":"All cooling equipment requires gas to be filled. During the services, the technician will check the gas level and if found short, it should be filled, otherwise the cooling capacity will be reduced. The company may offer free gas filling for 10 years as a promotional offer, as for good equipments, normally there's no such requirement of filling gas.see less","votes":"0","username":"Sasi TDPA","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell me what is total installation charge including drilling and stand?","answer":"Installation charge is 1200+GST=1415 RS and stand is 750 Rs","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is standard installation charges included in the cost or it has to be paid separately to the engineer post installation?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it include separate  stabilizer","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sasi TDPA","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Consumption shows per year , what is the daily runnig time?","answer":"Average 8 hrs","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Singal","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the installation chargeable? If yes then what are the charges ?","answer":"1415 rs","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Patel","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it perfect for 156sq.ft room size","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Kumar","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is a breakage in ac which we have noticed after the installation.....what can we do?","answer":"Replace","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac installation added means","answer":"Cost of installation added in the sale price.","votes":"0","username":"Sasi TDPA","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"It can control through mobile phone or not ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why AC remote stand is not provided in this model?","answer":"No stand provided","votes":"0","username":"RAJIV THAKUR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is supplier downtech electronics pvt ltd supplyong 3 meter interconnecting copper pipes and cable with this ac at the time of delivery","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"vishnu Marella","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"The offered price is included with installation charges?","answer":"Installation charges are excluded. However, better to arrange on your own, vendor's technicians are not trained and are unprofessional.","votes":"0","username":"M K K","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa61cfba6a7877c08b6"},"product_asin":"B09PZ1GZ8R","QAs":[{"question":"Kya ye dc supplie ko ac m convert karta hai","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i run in dc","answer":"No only AC","votes":"0","username":"SM Rehan Yousuf","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"2.5 kv inverter solar par chal jayga","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it will work on 2 kw load from Society meter?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if the ac is received in damaged condition","answer":"Simple return policy available, u can return within return policy terms.","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to switch off the red light as no button is working on it?","answer":"Red light is for clean filter reminder which remind you to clean filter after every 250 hr. Of your AC operation, for resting it press and hold both temp. Button on AC panel (not remote only AC panel), hope this helps","votes":"0","username":"I. Mishra","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"can I get any hot and cold window ac from this manufacturer","answer":"Yes u can","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What do me mean by 10 year warranty with gas charging? It means if gas leaks it will be filled free of cost?","answer":"Not satisfied with the cooling.","votes":"0","username":"mohd shariq","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is exchange offer on this","answer":"I exchange my ten yr old ehirlpool window ac in working condition for Rs. 4650.","votes":"0","username":"Animesh Srivastava","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is minimum kw required to run 1.5 ton window ac?","answer":"This AC consumes about 1450 W. So any load above 2 KV will be OK in my opinion . Pl take expert advice also based on your electricity requirement.","votes":"0","username":"Animesh Srivastava","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"When its price drop","answer":"Depends upon offers","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I avail the free services of the ordered AC?","answer":"Contact nearest lg service centre u can online it’s better platform","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units per hour","answer":"It’s completely depends upon your uses","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Convertible 4-in-1 ? What is it mean ?","answer":"You can adjust cooling capacity of 1.5 ton to 1.2 or .9 or .6 ton as per your requirement.","votes":"0","username":"Narendra Singh","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this model good for 11*14 room?  Will it cool fast or i should go for 5star model?","answer":"Its good for 11×14 size room, and fast cooling","votes":"0","username":"PRADEEP J.","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya solar se bhi chal skta h?","answer":"Kindly ask a valid question","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why you have increased price exorbitantly to 39999 for this 4star model?? It was selling at 29000 in March 22. 10000 costly","answer":"It’s not solar powered","votes":"0","username":"R Mathur","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"कितना एरिया कवर करता है","answer":"150-200 sq feet","votes":"0","username":"anil kumar","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Price in lucknow","answer":"Same price for all over India as price shown in offer list","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is It fast cooling?","answer":"No there is no turbo cooling","votes":"0","username":"PRADEEP J.","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is green gas","answer":"Yes R32","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can We install it in a stand as a coolers in a room,","answer":"U can, but window fixed is better for stability without any risk of damage","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is power consumption per hour?","answer":"If u set 26-28 degrees then approx is less than 1units","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it export from thiland?","answer":"Yes completely Thailand brand","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"how mani temp.work  maximum","answer":"16 to 30","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many maximum temp. work .l.g. window a.c","answer":"16 to 30","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"this ac can we put in fully close room without window","answer":"Fully closed room you have,This ac performance is very perfect.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Agar isse 1 gante chalege to kitni biji consume hogi","answer":"Wo apke upper depend haiApko Kitna temp set krna hMene to 27-28*c set kr ke 6hr chalaya tha to 2unit aya thaEse v electricity bill kama ayega compare to non inverter Acsee less","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"how to get free services in a one year","answer":"As per lg term and condition","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the price?","answer":"As I compared to lg distributor off line is 33500 and extra installation charges","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Isme outdoor blower ka jarurat nahi hai kya","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"my window is 65 cm in length. will this ac fit ?? Plz reply i want to buy this product.","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"my vindo size is 60 cm and 40 cm does it will fit ???","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this automatically cut off soon as set temperature is attained in the room?","answer":"No, its continued runMaking lots of notice, sometimes abnormal sound tooFan notice is also muchsee less","votes":"0","username":"sagar kumar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have cement roof sheet and that heats a lot will this AC justify its cooling in such conditions","answer":"Its perfect function as an concrete roof.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"If run the ac for 8hrs how many units will it consumes??","answer":"If u set 27-28*c then it’s approx 2unit to 2.5units will consume","votes":"0","username":"Er. Ajit Nayak, Chandigarh","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange my old window AC","answer":"Yes, the seller gave me exchange option","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many free wet services do we have from LG?","answer":"yes two service free","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges is included or not as in the discription it is showing installation added.","answer":"No installation charges are not including","votes":"0","username":"PRADEEP J.","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is k sath kaisa stabiliser thik rahega?","answer":"This AC already have internal stablizer, but better to the external one. I am using V Guard (VG 400), working fine,","votes":"0","username":"pawan","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac is making around 60 db noise. doesn't sound like noiseless!","answer":"It's noisy","votes":"0","username":"PRADEEP J.","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"I recieved 2021 model but seller mention on website 2022 model what I do?? ?","answer":"4 star model 2022 model","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the gairntee period?","answer":"5 years and 10 years on compressor","votes":"0","username":"PRADEEP J.","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"बैट्री कि ओसेकता है","answer":"THE BATTERIES FOR THE REMOTE WERE RECEIVED IN THE PACKAGE","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"This price is with gst or without gst?","answer":"Price is with GST.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exterior fan isme hota hai ya nahi?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya ismein stabilizer Lagana jaruri h","answer":"Haan, Agar AC jyada saal chalana hai to","votes":"0","username":"I. Mishra","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या एसी को लगातार 1.5 ton से 1ton में  परिवर्तित किया जा सकता है","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"anil kumar","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to connect with mobile apk","answer":"This model deos not have connectivity option, only 5 star model has wifi connectivity","votes":"0","username":"I. Mishra","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have received my Ac yesterday now how much the brand will take to call me for installation","answer":"I have received call for installation same-day as delivery but if you haven't got any call within 48 hrs. Then call lg customer care","votes":"0","username":"I. Mishra","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb include in it or not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"sagar kumar","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My window size is 56cm width. Will it fit?","answer":"26/18 SIZ","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kitne degree temperature tak kam karta h","answer":"52","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa71cfba6a7877c08ee"},"product_asin":"B09WRG7HDV","QAs":[{"question":"Is it work with alexa?","answer":"Nope,this is not wifi enabled AC","votes":"0","username":"Ishtiaque","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sir installation ka charge company pay kare gi ya consumer ko pay karna hai...","answer":"Consumer","votes":"0","username":"Sharang Sharma","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get gst invoice","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Althaf…","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this comes with 5 years PCB warranty?","answer":"Yes but don't buy very disappointed ☹️ no cooling i have buy before 10 days i am not satisfied","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Nigam","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation free or chargeable?","answer":"Chargeable. 1199+tax. Total 1500 for installation. Stand charges will be different than that. Which is around 800-1200 deending on what the lg guy brings in with. Approx 2500 additional to pay with this which is pathetic.","votes":"0","username":"Jay","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this prouduct is hot and cold","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Sharang Sharma","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"200 sqft kmre me achhi kaam kregi","answer":"120 sqft me sahi hai","votes":"0","username":"Prakash Singh Baghel","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need a stablizer with the AC?","answer":"Not to need stabilizer with this AC","votes":"0","username":"DEBRAJ MUKHERJEE","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inthis model whether both swing works?","answer":"Nope only 1 swing works ..which is up and down.  If you want you go can for VIRAT series for much better infact best cooling and 5star rated model.","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 star vs 4 star electric bill consumption same","answer":"Almost same","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Nigam","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the installation charges payable to the technician or it is included in the price? Is the making hole in the wall chargeable?","answer":"Before getting an AC, please make sure that you call electrician and get 1 16 ampere box installed for its main power connection.","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's swing 4way or not","answer":"Nope this model has only 1 way which is up and down","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do i show ac working in dismantled condition","answer":"Do not have any idea but i don't think so this is possible but you can always contact an AC technician for doing this.","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is a prices of copper wire per miter","answer":"Depends on brand to brand. Please check with the customer support of the brand whose AC you are planning to get.","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stand free ??","answer":"Nope stand is chargeable","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the difference between  ps-q19rnye and ps-q18knye?","answer":"Please compare these models in 2 areas :-","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lowest coling capacity?","answer":"16 degrees","votes":"0","username":"Sharang Sharma","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is meaning of \"Warranty Type\tLimited\" ???","answer":"It may be a seller's warranty and not the direct manufacturer's warranty.","votes":"0","username":"Maddy's Love","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"4 way swing?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"anand","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa81cfba6a7877c0904"},"product_asin":"B09NS5K7HF","QAs":[{"question":"How many units of power does it consumes","answer":"Packing was not good and AC fall down in front of us so we rejected","votes":"0","username":"Naren","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it waterproof?","answer":"Yes Go for it","votes":"0","username":"Amar kumar","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"lg ps-q19ynze need stablizer?","answer":"If there is no power fluctuations in your area. Then no need of stabilizer. Otherwise for safety take stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"Rohit K.","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation charge added in this price?","answer":"No, installation charges are 2500 including 3 drain pipe and wall mount stand for outdoor unit","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get dublicate remote from LG as my son damaged the old one?","answer":"Yes it's approximately rs 3000","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac hot and cooling???","answer":"Only cool","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"inbuilt stabilizer?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is instalation service available in Vrindavan 281121","answer":"Yes it's available there","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote hoder received yes  or not","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold ac with 5star rating","answer":"Only cold with 5star rating","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या ये सर्दी मे गर्मी भी दे सकता हैं ?","answer":"Nhii","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Safe to run on 3kva inverter without damaging AC?","answer":"3kva  ?","votes":"0","username":"Simranjeet","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer use...?","answer":"No need if you have proper voltage,and little fluctuations,but for safety of pcb, you can use stablizer","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"In description it is mentioned as “lg 1.5 ton 5 star ai dual inverter wi-fi split ac\" but couple of questions are answered as no wifi. kindly confirm.","answer":"Wifi version is supirior and cost more than non wifi version","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Safe to run on 3kva inverter without damaging AC?","answer":"I think yes,maximum wattage is 1.5 ke,you can also run on 80%,60% or 40% to save power consumption","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lg service very bad why","answer":"It is true,because parts are not available on the service centre immediately","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need stabilizer...?  lg psq19wzf 1.5 ton","answer":"better have it for dual safety of any AC","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer use...?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why cooling at 52 degree is not advertised for this product? Is cooling unaffected till 52 degrees by this product?","answer":"This AC with dual inverter and 5 star rating is good for saving electricity but defeat the purpose of cooling if temperature is little bit high 35 + Celsius. So my advice avoid this model and don't get attracted toward  dual inverter with 5 star rating kind of add on which defeat the purpose of AC.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I connect this to Alexa?","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the power consumption at 40% capacity?","answer":"0.6 ton power consumption at 40 percent","votes":"0","username":"gaurav","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa81cfba6a7877c0931"},"product_asin":"B09NS5TKPN","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have Anti mosquito technology ?","answer":"Anti virus technology...","votes":"0","username":"Amar kumar","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ye inverter pr bhi kam krta h kya","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ye jo lg ka ac abhi dekha gaya hai kya isme hot and cool dono hai","answer":"Noo","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ac is suitable for 225 sq feet room?","answer":"Hello,I'm using it for approximately 200 sq feet and it is more than enough to cool it comfortably within ten minutes. This is the best air conditioner I ever bought. The energy-saving mode really helps in saving electricity cost. Sleep mode gradually adjusts the temperature (a very intelligent machine). I'm comprehensively satisfied with this LG 1.5-ton AC.see less","votes":"0","username":"M. Shaikh","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does the add installation card means here?","answer":"It's just a notification to the brand thing.. you don't need to pay for it during purchase. You have to pay the said installation price directly to the LG engineer. Hope this helps..!!","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible with Alexa?","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Shreshtha","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have heat mode?","answer":"No, only cooling.","votes":"0","username":"ksk","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange AC will be removed by whom? Is there any charge","answer":"The same guy will remove but will charge 500-750 rs","votes":"0","username":"Tittle JOSEPH","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it cool 225 sqft room?","answer":"Yes definitely...go for it...","votes":"0","username":"Amar kumar","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling up to which temperature","answer":"Superb 👍👌","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the outdoor temprature cooling capacity?","answer":"LG AC is good but Amazon misguided to people about the installation. When I purchase the AC AMAZON commit that installation is free but it's totally wrong. Installation is chargeable approx 1800 . Please be aware before the purchase through Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Syed adil","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ac flap take howmuch time to close when we off ac from remote","answer":"Superb 👍👌","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ye kitni bijli leta hai","answer":"Per hour 1 unit","votes":"-1","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to contact for service","answer":"Superb 👍👌","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do LG offer provide free installation?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it need Stabilizer","answer":"Yes for better efficiency..but work normally without it too","votes":"0","username":"Chandan","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this both hot and cold?","answer":"Superb 👍👌","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this AC has temperature display?","answer":"Yes it has a display which lg called magic display","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we trust the seller?","answer":"Yes i recieved a fresh manufacturing 13 may 22 product","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ek din kitna energy legi","answer":"It's depends on usage and the floor location if your room expose to direct sunlight thaen 6 to 7 unit a day and not than only 5 unit for 8 to 10 hours","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"if the pipe or anything else is missing in box then what should i do ?","answer":"You can return product and asked for a new piece...return policy applicable","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"if the shortage in pipe then i should pay for this ?? or the installation guy will figure it out","answer":"Installing pipe was not in it","votes":"0","username":"Preetam","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's is possible to Run 1.5 ton ac on single phase line comes for long distance","answer":"No. Not at all advisable","votes":"0","username":"BPC Rao","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"2 killo watt power supply can connect","answer":"Yes it's more about voltage and not the power","votes":"0","username":"Ishan Mahajan","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ‎ps-q19ynze 2022 model have a 4-way swing?","answer":"It has 6 way swing with artificial intelligence","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the cast of extra copper pipe per meter?","answer":"Around Rs 1000","votes":"0","username":"BPC Rao","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What charges we have to pay for technician","answer":"1199+ gst for labour","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whom to contact for installation??? A as installation added so might the service engineer come or we need to contact them?????","answer":"After your product delivered ,lg service call you within 24 hours","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Refrigerant  used R32 or any other?","answer":"R32","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi please let me the know the measurement of the outdoor unit (width, height and depth)","answer":"It's 3x2 feet","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"If outside temperature is 45 celsius, and we run this ac at 16 celsius, what would be the reduced room temperature if ac operates continuously?","answer":"It's works even outside temperature is more than 45 ,you can check through your remote room temperature","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"\"brand installation support\" is listed as rs. 0. does that mean installation is free, or will standard charge apply?","answer":"It's chargeble","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is its working in winter also as hot temperature please answer?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"एलजी 1.5 टन एसी के इंस्टॉलेशन चार्जेस क्या है","answer":"Rs.1199+ 18%GST=1415 Rs.","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar Gupta Advocate Hi…","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges kya hai","answer":"1500","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling wattage , air flow rate and weight of indoor and outdoor units","answer":"5000wAir flowin636Out1520Indoor 14 kgOutdoor 33kgsee less","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i have required more than 4 mts copper pipe then how we take it. we","answer":"950 per meter","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the hn and jn model with 5star lg 1.5 ton. explain in detail, what is the difference?","answer":"Superb 👍👌","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want billing on corporate office","answer":"Superb 👌👍","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to add my gst number in the invoice","answer":"You need to create a business account on Amazon for which you need to fill all the details required. After it is approved by Amazon which eventually takes 2 to 3 working days your account will be changed to Amazon Business account and you will get GST invoices for the eligible products","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is thst mode 5 AI will do","answer":"You can set it to work at 80,60 or 40 percent capacity if less crowded. Supposed to save electricity.","votes":"0","username":"Ashish Chauhan","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of the drain pipe included in the box?","answer":"No drain pipe provide in package","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh Kulkarni","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this ac ( model ps-q19ynze )have remote control holder ?","answer":"No.. Doesn't received remote holder","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Procedure of services","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Lovepreet Singh Brar","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How come suddenly maximum exchange value decrease from 4000 to 1200?","answer":"It's depends on third party exchange partner","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which split AC has powerfull Wind blowing?","answer":"Daikin","votes":"0","username":"Meghana Gaddam","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether copper tube is provided in the box ?","answer":"I purchased two 1.5 ton ACs with 3 days gap. In one of them copper pipe was missing. But When I reported to Amazon & forwarded a copy of LG installation report that mentioned this, Amazon refunded major portion of the Cu pipe cost.","votes":"0","username":"BPC Rao","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the Installation be done in another place?","answer":"yes,  you can call the LG customer care and ask them to install any where you wants","votes":"0","username":"Sujeet Kumar Teotia","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Add ac installation means free installation","answer":"Its not free they charged around Rs. 1450 extra for the installation","votes":"0","username":"Sujeet Kumar Teotia","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Missing copper installation pipes. How can I return this order?","answer":"Installation guys bring it normally","votes":"0","username":"Tittle JOSEPH","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"In Ac box , both the copper wire and the copper pipe will be 3 meters.","answer":"Yes both are provided","votes":"0","username":"JAGATBIT","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mesion work is included in Installation","answer":"Installation is chargable by customer however amazon said its free. Be aware","votes":"0","username":"Syed adil","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the Installation be done in a different location?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"dipankar biswas","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"do we have to fit the plug point ourselves or will the installation people do it?","answer":"Installation person usually don't install the power plug etc. Yet you may ask to do the same for some extra cash payment to them.. it will be their extra income.. hope you understood what I'm trying to explain.. 😉","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units of power does it consumes per hour","answer":"I'm using this AC for more than 20 hours a day @ 25~26 degree and my overall power consumption increased from 6~7 units to 15~17 units.. hope this explains.. also I've installed this AC in a direct sun exposure room","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Service team collect money for installation","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"dipankar biswas","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Service fee","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"dipankar biswas","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this ynze or enze model ? because ynze is 4star model and enze is 5 star.. but you mentioned 5 star with ynze. this is misleading","answer":"I have mentioned in 5 star model only not 4star","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free hai kya","answer":"Nai","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free hai is ke saat","answer":"Paid installation","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"power connection provided in indoor or outdoor?\r\nWhether power cord is supplied?","answer":"Power cable provided for indoor unit.","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"My room is 14*16 feet height is 11 feet on top floor is it work","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What gas does it have?","answer":"R-32","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include 3 meter copper wire ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Srinivas Chikkudu","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is all instrument and installation charge added in this price?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be suitable for 160sqft room ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is arate this ac","answer":"10*","votes":"0","username":"dipankar biswas","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"In label Model year is 2021. But in description they mentioned 2022. Will get 2022 model or 2021 model?","answer":"They are sending worng dated products and also sending the wrong set of Indore and outdoor units. The seller is so careless that he doesn't even bother to see what products are being sent out. Please don't make the payments in advance as my payment is still not refunded for more than 11 days.","votes":"0","username":"Amit Sharma","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"does warranty covers gas filling on second day of  installation?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the diferrence between q19rnze and q19ynze model?","answer":"One has wifi feature and another doesn't","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many watt take this ac","answer":"1 unit for 3 hours","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"O d u weight","answer":"35 kh","votes":"0","username":"Sagar Patil","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it also comes with darinage pipe?","answer":"No. It doesn't.","votes":"0","username":"Aishee","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"After sales service?","answer":"Very nice in my area","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many ton ac require room size 14*12?","answer":"Thumb rule says 1 ton for 100 Sq.ft wherein 4 people are being considered","votes":"0","username":"Arindam Ghosh","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the performance in peek summer or in the hot noon outside ?","answer":"It performs more than expectation, like it cools faster than conventional AC when outside temperature is 39 - 40 degee centigrade and maintains the set temperature as long it runs, most interesting part is that you can run this AC longer than conventional AC and generates almost half electricity bill than conventional AC","votes":"0","username":"Arindam Ghosh","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is instalation  free as mentioned in the product page??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"R JAGAN MOHAN RAO","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is they are providing cooper wire nowdays","answer":"They have not provided even after lodging complaint. Very updated with poor customer service.  No response.","votes":"0","username":"R JAGAN MOHAN RAO","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the pcb meaning","answer":"Printed circuit board","votes":"0","username":"Kushagra Bansal","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free?","answer":"No, Rs. 1414 + ( 750 - 1000 ) more if external stand opted.","votes":"0","username":"Satyaranjan Nayak","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model? 2022 or before","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"ksk","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper pipe included?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ksk","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does ac fan runs in sleep mode?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"R JAGAN MOHAN RAO","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the compressor max ambient temperature operation rating?","answer":"52","votes":"0","username":"Tittle JOSEPH","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free?","answer":"No, installation is not free. Even not hasslefree also. The after selling service of LG is bad. They sent a technician after 12 times of calling to customer care and 5 others including Amazon. A totally inexperienced technician came, did all in unprofessional way and even broke the fiber cover of indoor unit. Thats the conclusion. Decided to take AC from only physical shops and will take the risk of installing by my known technician. No one to blame. Its me, who did buy the product of LG further from Amazom.see less","votes":"0","username":"SUBHRO MONDAL","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have standard copper pipe?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SUBHRO MONDAL","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much Electricity bill","answer":"Just for reference, we were having monthly bill of roughly 700 Rs, after moderate use of AC in 25 degree, our first 15 days bill came as 1400 Rs.","votes":"0","username":"Satyaranjan Nayak","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between ps-q19ynze and ps-q19rnze","answer":"Researched. But seems to be market gimmick.","votes":"0","username":"SUBHRO MONDAL","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is gas recharge free for 10 years? As written in warrenty","answer":"May be. But LG's after selling service is worst. So if possible,i will do from outside.","votes":"0","username":"SUBHRO MONDAL","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How length of the copper wire","answer":"10 feet","votes":"0","username":"Satyaranjan Nayak","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation free?.Stabizer will be given free ?","answer":"Installation is not free, Stabilizer is chargable, also it is not required if you have stable voltage with not much of fluctuations","votes":"0","username":"Satyaranjan Nayak","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper pipe kit include","answer":"Not include.","votes":"0","username":"anilbabu","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"how much inter conncting pipe","answer":"They don't provide any interconnect pipe we need to buy cost of 3500/-","votes":"0","username":"Pvbsudhakar","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"But in the billing installation was added right why are you charging for that...Then?","answer":"We have to pay 2000/-to the technecian.","votes":"0","username":"anilbabu","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can I get earlye","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"anilbabu","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"819watt/year ?? Usage hours or per day energy consumption?","answer":"We use from night 8 pm to morning 7 am at 26 deg C. Power consumption observed is 4 units per day. Initially consumes around 1850 watts, then gradually reduces and stabilizes to around 300 watts for most of the time.","votes":"0","username":"Mariapaul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with pipes to connect indoor unit with outdoor unit ??","answer":"One has to pay for pipes as per the length required and charge at a rate per meter","votes":"0","username":"B Mallikanadh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit copper or alluminium","answer":"You may have choice. Rate changes with material","votes":"0","username":"B Mallikanadh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the installation free or else how much they charge overall?","answer":"Rs. 1400 for installation and Rs.900 for stand(inclusive of GST)","votes":"0","username":"Mariapaul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will remote stand/holder be also be part of assessories. recently i have purchased ac but not received remote holder.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RAVI D","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which is better lg or panasonic in 1.5 ton with 5 star rating?","answer":"No Doubt Sir, Go for the LG Other Brands are Fail Now in AC","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Sharma","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you need stablizer","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Agha sahib","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या ये सर्दी मे गर्मी भी दे सकता हैं ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar Gupta Advocate Hi…","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"installation charge free","answer":"No, but charge is less compared to normal charge, always recomend to do the installation by company technician only","votes":"0","username":"Arindam Ghosh","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please clarify the product code of 2022 1.5 ton 5 star ai dual 6 in 1. as product code is different on amazon it must be of ps-q19rnze not ps-q19ynze.","answer":"This is the product code PS-Q19YNZE in amazon so as the delivered product","votes":"0","username":"vijaya sai krishna toleti","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hut and cold both?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stablizer is required","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you suggest a best stabilizer for lg 1.5 ton ac 5 star ps q19ynze  model","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is this model different than ps-q19bnze? which one is recommended?","answer":"2022 model","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Low cooling process how to raise complaint","answer":"True, the cooling is very low. need to claim to LG service center and also provide the product feedback in Amazon as the other users do not buy this product","votes":"0","username":"vijaya sai krishna toleti","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the price including the fixing charges","answer":"installation charges, extra as per the specification in Amazon","votes":"0","username":"vijaya sai krishna toleti","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any bagk light for remote?","answer":"NO, It should have been there.","votes":"0","username":"Sharad Patel","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the length of the pipe ? What's the cost of extra pipe per foot ?","answer":"It was 3 meters long , not sure about cost for extra length","votes":"0","username":"i.chandrasekharreddy","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"AC installation is added in my order by default. Do I have to pay charges for installation ?? (Date 13/04/22)","answer":"Yes, You have to pay Installation charges 1200 + Tax and for outside Ac stand 800 + tax. (1400 + 900).","votes":"0","username":"Gulab Singh pal","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we also need stabilizer for this.","answer":"Yes, Bring Bluebird stabilizer for better performance.","votes":"0","username":"Gulab Singh pal","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Connecting copper pipes will come along with product or not?some reviews saying no copper pipe in package","answer":"The AC does come with copper wire but it is only 2 feet. According to your fitting position, if the given 2 feet copper wire is insufficient you need to buy from the installation guys.","votes":"0","username":"Anindya Biswas","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या एलजी कंपनी वाले कॉपर पाइप अंडरग्राउंड कर कर देते हैं","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar Gupta Advocate Hi…","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hlo sir , sir lg ka ac online ya offlines purchase karo uski warranty pcb or compresser ki kahi ragister krne ke baad activ hoti hain ya purchase krne","answer":"Online price is always less than offline provided there is offer going on, online. But you buy only from LG Store, you will get a one year extra warranty than provided by online purchase.","votes":"0","username":"Anindya Biswas","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is copper condenser?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"M MAHABOOBBASHA","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"LG engenee team asking 5000rs for installation AC...?","answer":"1500","votes":"0","username":"M MAHABOOBBASHA","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Wi-Fi ac","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anindya Biswas","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does 6-in-1 convertible mean?","answer":"6 in 1 convertable means making you fool.","votes":"0","username":"Gulab Singh pal","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it include 10 feet copper wire and stand?","answer":"No extra copper wire or stand is included in the package, it contains just the AC. During installation, you have to buy the stand and Cooper wires separately.","votes":"0","username":"Ananda Shankar Basu","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या एलजी एसी इंस्टॉल के साथ स्टैंड और गैस फ्री है","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Kumar Gupta Advocate Hi…","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it need to have stabili","answer":"Not compulsory… it works well without stabiliser for past 8 months…. No issues….","votes":"0","username":"Doc kumar","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the pcb warranty. Both on external and internal ?","answer":"5 years","votes":"0","username":"john ratnakar","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is paid or free?","answer":"Absolutely free… but they’ll charge for extra length copper wires if basic length not sufficient….","votes":"0","username":"Doc kumar","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"HAS","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper wire missing in box","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"john ratnakar","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is free installation for this product? What does add installation mean?","answer":"Instalation is not free. It cost 1500rs. Stand is extra 700 and stand fixing charges 250.","votes":"0","username":"john ratnakar","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it waterproof?","answer":"Yes Go for it","votes":"0","username":"Amar kumar","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"lg ps-q19ynze need stablizer?","answer":"If there is no power fluctuations in your area. Then no need of stabilizer. Otherwise for safety take stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"Rohit K.","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation charge added in this price?","answer":"No, installation charges are 2500 including 3 drain pipe and wall mount stand for outdoor unit","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get dublicate remote from LG as my son damaged the old one?","answer":"Yes it's approximately rs 3000","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac hot and cooling???","answer":"Only cool","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"inbuilt stabilizer?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is instalation service available in Vrindavan 281121","answer":"Yes it's available there","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Remote hoder received yes  or not","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold ac with 5star rating","answer":"Only cold with 5star rating","votes":"0","username":"Anupam Rana","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या ये सर्दी मे गर्मी भी दे सकता हैं ?","answer":"Nhii","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Safe to run on 3kva inverter without damaging AC?","answer":"3kva  ?","votes":"0","username":"Simranjeet","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer use...?","answer":"No need if you have proper voltage,and little fluctuations,but for safety of pcb, you can use stablizer","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"In description it is mentioned as “lg 1.5 ton 5 star ai dual inverter wi-fi split ac\" but couple of questions are answered as no wifi. kindly confirm.","answer":"Wifi version is supirior and cost more than non wifi version","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Safe to run on 3kva inverter without damaging AC?","answer":"I think yes,maximum wattage is 1.5 ke,you can also run on 80%,60% or 40% to save power consumption","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lg service very bad why","answer":"It is true,because parts are not available on the service centre immediately","votes":"0","username":"Rajneesh Kumar Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need stabilizer...?  lg psq19wzf 1.5 ton","answer":"better have it for dual safety of any AC","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer use...?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why cooling at 52 degree is not advertised for this product? Is cooling unaffected till 52 degrees by this product?","answer":"This AC with dual inverter and 5 star rating is good for saving electricity but defeat the purpose of cooling if temperature is little bit high 35 + Celsius. So my advice avoid this model and don't get attracted toward  dual inverter with 5 star rating kind of add on which defeat the purpose of AC.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I connect this to Alexa?","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the power consumption at 40% capacity?","answer":"0.6 ton power consumption at 40 percent","votes":"0","username":"gaurav","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa91cfba6a7877c0950"},"product_asin":"B082TGK3K8","QAs":[{"question":"Heat also?","answer":"No. It's meant for cooling alone","votes":"0","username":"Akash Rana","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"manufacturing date","answer":"2020 model","votes":"0","username":"DRSANJAY S.","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do I have to buy a battery also to power this ac","answer":"NO","votes":"0","username":"Shilpaben Bharatkumar Rangrej","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we install it above 5 feet window section?","answer":"I am guessing you mean 5 feet above the ground . Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhijit khuranna","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya ye only batteries se chalta hai","answer":"Light chahiye","votes":"0","username":"Jagat","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What should be the ideal size of window for smooth installation of this unit?","answer":"200-250sqft","votes":"0","username":"nayan","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Swing how to adjust it in a room","answer":"There is no vertical swing however horizontal manual adjustment swing is there. It cools the room significantly good that there is no need of swing.","votes":"0","username":"Jagat","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the delivery associate uninstall the current one on payment of charges?","answer":"No you have to do that earlier","votes":"0","username":"nayan","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units will it take if I run it continuously for 12 hours?","answer":"12","votes":"0","username":"Jagat","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the diff between 2020 and 2022 model?","answer":"Price","votes":"0","username":"Jagat","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"After delivery, how is installation scheduled and how long does it take?","answer":"In my case it was installed on the same day. ONE SMS will come with details of person/shop/contact who will come for the installation.","votes":"0","username":"SUJOY DAS","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is customer care number","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"DRSANJAY S.","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it display temp in fahrenheit or in celcius?","answer":"Celcius","votes":"0","username":"Heena","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need stabilizer for this AC?","answer":"No need","votes":"0","username":"Heena","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is dual inverter windows ac","answer":"Yes, it is a dual inverter window AC.","votes":"0","username":"Shubham Srivastava","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pcb warranty for 5 years ?","answer":"if installation by company person pcb warranty 5year.","votes":"0","username":"mandeep","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the year of manufacture 2020 or 2022?","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"Shubham Srivastava","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"एलजी विंडो एसी 1 दिन में कितने यूनिट बिजली खर्च होती है","answer":"As per your uses. 1 hr per 1 unit.","votes":"0","username":"Mohd Arshad Ziya","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it run on electricity .or battery","answer":"Battery only for covert from ac to dc","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation is free?","answer":"no chargeable 500+90(gst)","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation free since it says instalation added?","answer":"no, this is chargeable 590 rs","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I see room temperature in display?","answer":"Nop","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling capacity?","answer":"Its good","votes":"0","username":"PRASANTA BHOWMIK","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is 2022 model?","answer":"nop this is 2020 model","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is this 2020 model different from current 2022 Model?","answer":"technology","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is paid annual maintenance service charges for this AC after 1 Year.","answer":"Totally free of cost","votes":"0","username":"Dishant Rana","date":"2022-04-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturer is showing as lg thailand. will  lg provide warranty coverage in india?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"window L G air conditionar with Hot and cold and inverter","answer":"Nope only cold,its not H&C model","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"In case of exchange, Will the person come to pick the old ac will do uninstallation as well?","answer":"Nope,you will have to keep it ready for just pickup","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warrety terms say 10 year on compressor with gas charging do we need to buy extended warranty then?","answer":"Yes definately if you want to keep the rest of the machine tensionfree","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is made in thailand or made in india?","answer":"Thailand","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Outdoor unit is available or not in this ac?","answer":"Windows dont have 2 units","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the size","answer":"mentioned in pictures","votes":"0","username":"Vivek Batra","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can someone tell me the exact pcb warranty for this lg product. i don't see this on the website.","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this have pcb 5 years warranty","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any new model for 2022?? This 5 star Bee rating is still valid (as it is showing till 2020)??","answer":"Yes… every year the rating refreshes.. if will be around 3.5 star in 2022","votes":"0","username":"souptik","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference btw jw-q18wuza 2020 and pw-q18wuza 2022 mode. 2022 model is 2000 cheaper than 2020?","answer":"The filter ..","votes":"0","username":"Virendra Pratap Singh","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या सोलर प्लेट भी साथ मे है","answer":"koi bhin solar plate sath me nahi aayi hai","votes":"0","username":"Mahesh Chandra Meena","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या ये बैटरी से चलेगा  पावर स्रोत बैटरी है","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"RK","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fa91cfba6a7877c0966"},"product_asin":"B09NS4BRK3","QAs":[{"question":"What is the ambient temperature above which this AC will stop cooling?","answer":"16 degree Celsius","votes":"0","username":"Yash","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it connect with wifi  thin q lg app or it has wifi option","answer":"No, no wifi","votes":"0","username":"P R G S Gupta","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"It has wifi?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prashant Sahoo","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this sufficient for 250 square feet?","answer":"2 ton is not needed for 250 sq ft. 1 ton is more than adequate.","votes":"0","username":"Nishit Kumar","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whate is required capacity for 350 sqf","answer":"I am using 2 ton LG 2022 model but only 30 to 40% of my room feels cooled , my room size is 250 sq ft, so you should check more than 2 ton or any other power full ac which performs well as that company say in any of the brand like hitachi, panasonic ,daikin, o general claims, don't expect alot with LG this model ac. I also complained about this to LG support and the technical team also visit but they sad that it is working fine even in front of them the ac remote was showing decreasing temperature near to the ac but when put the remote away from that area there was no change in the room temperature for long time , if they were correct than it means LG ac's are not efficient for much bigger room size. I also have 1.5 ton LG window ac that chilled my room efficiently.see less","votes":"0","username":"varun verma","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manual and warranty card not provided in the box. What needs to be done.","answer":"Connect to support team they can help.","votes":"0","username":"varun verma","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper pipe","answer":"if copper pipe is mising then just return the item.","votes":"0","username":"varun verma","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want 3 split ac and one compressor","answer":"This is combination is not available in standard models offered by LG. You may contact customer care to check further.","votes":"0","username":"Prashant Sahoo","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Minimum room temperature it can maintain continuously","answer":"I have installed it in living room but it failed to maintain temperature below 20 even after continuous use of 4 hours.","votes":"0","username":"abhi","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is 2 ton suitable for 275 sq ft room which also has an attached kitchen?","answer":"Yes of course","votes":"0","username":"Prasad Subramaniam","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pipe is included with ac or required to buy sparate ?","answer":"Small pipe include","votes":"0","username":"Fashion daddy","date":"2022-04-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3faa1cfba6a7877c098e"},"product_asin":"B09NS5Y4BG","QAs":[{"question":"During this AC installation  whether outer unit stand installation charges are paid seperately or the amount of 1416 includes this work","answer":"Outer unit stand installation charges are needed to be paid .","votes":"0","username":"KKG","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why cant we get it install from local engineer ??","answer":"You can","votes":"0","username":"KKG","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is inner unit size?","answer":"99 Centimetres","votes":"0","username":"Jayesh Gandhi","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"have anyone purchased this product at 31k???","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is not free chargable by brand + charge of any extra work including stand","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it Stablizer required or not?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have copper pipe along with pack","answer":"No. Copper pipe was mentioned but was not shipped with it.But Amazon refunded me 2250 for it. Just ask the LG service guy to provide you JOB card and mention on it that \"copper pipe missing\".In submission of copy of  job card to Amazon.Amazon will refund you.see less","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this lg ac need stabilizer?","answer":"No, this ac does not require stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How it is different from ps-q19gwzf ? i ordered ps-q19swzf but got ps-q19gwzf, is the color only difference ?","answer":"Working and performance are same","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is pcb warranty on both indoor and outdoor units","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"In 55 degrees this product works","answer":"Yes but will take more time to cool the room.Also depends on room size and direct sunlight","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is installation  of LG ac paid","answer":"Yes.. it is paid. also interconnecting pipe was not there in the box when opened. So it costed 6000 extra + installation charge","votes":"0","username":"A_C","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation cost","answer":"1415","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot & cool ac","answer":"Cool","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it Works with alexa?","answer":"No wifi in thi model","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many swings are there? Is it worthy product to go for?","answer":"just the vertical scroll. Would suggest getting this offline, as this does not come with copper pipe for installation, which is a additional cost.","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units of electricity does it consume in every hour?","answer":"At 100% 1.5 unit per hour","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need stabilizer 4 star ac","answer":"the unit can handle fluctuations up toa range, but if voltage fluctuates beyond that.. better to opt for a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this unit include Copper wire?","answer":"Not given","votes":"0","username":"Dasu Babu Talari","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many free services are provided with this AC??","answer":"Three","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation is free or not?","answer":"its not free, only scheduling installation is free. 1199+taxes, any additional work is charged extra","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is both Horizontal and vertical swing available","answer":"only vertical","votes":"-1","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it need a stabilizer?","answer":"Still I am using without stabilizer.","votes":"0","username":"aashish vatsa","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they provide Remote control holder","answer":"no holder is not included","votes":"0","username":"sandeep","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Set 16 temp.  How many units in 1 hrs","answer":"Mujhe 16° krne ki zarurat nahi padi abhi tak 24 pr hi chalata hu","votes":"0","username":"Saras Shukla","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the installation free or paid ?","answer":"Paid. I paid 2575-/ including stand and extra drain pipe.","votes":"0","username":"aashish vatsa","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is outdoor unit size","answer":"Normal size,not bulky","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is out door unit size?","answer":"Standard size","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Some latest reviews saying \"Copper wire missing\", is it true?","answer":"Not true","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between lg dual inverter 5in1 convertible 4 star split ac model ps q19rnye and ps q19jnye?","answer":"Almost same as per user requirements","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Insulation charge free??","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's highest cooling capacity of this AC?","answer":"110%","votes":"0","username":"M MAHABOOBBASHA","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How i check if delivered product has ThinQ/Wifi feature?","answer":"There is a logo of ThinQ (A home photo with ThinQ written below) on the machine. If not there then it's without Wifi and ThinQ.","votes":"0","username":"Sharad Patel","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product has AI(artificial intelligence)?","answer":"I think NO.","votes":"0","username":"aashish vatsa","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Idu and odu pcb warranty kitne year ki hai?","answer":"5 year pcb","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi guys, i just have 1 question is the installation by lg really that costly as some people have mentioned in the comments section? (2022 model)","answer":"1500 installation","votes":"0","username":"M MAHABOOBBASHA","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What amp power socket to be fixed to plug ac power socket","answer":"15","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper wire is missing?","answer":"Yes. But Amazon will refund 2250 on producing JOB card.","votes":"0","username":"ajay kumar","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why there is no copper pipe","answer":"It's missing, this question supposed to be ask with dealer","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"In description and detail it shows 2022 model but in image as shown 2021 model which is create confusions be clear which year is this model have","answer":"Product discription while purchasing is 2022 but on box manufacture date was of December 2021","votes":"0","username":"SKY","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this hot and cold ac?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SKY","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Desplay can be off or not","answer":"Off","votes":"0","username":"SKY","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturer Warranty10 Years on Compressor with gas charging...does this mean to cover free gas refilling for 10 years in case of gas leakage","answer":"No, free gas charging is done only when compressure is replaced/faulty.","votes":"0","username":"kirpal","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"4 way swing?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"anand","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fab1cfba6a7877c099d"},"product_asin":"B09NS5G1F9","QAs":[{"question":"You mentioned *lifetime warranty* and this is a wifi ac ???","answer":"Yes it is Wi-Fi AC will be connected using LG ThinQ app","votes":"0","username":"Uday Kanth C","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Size of outdoor unit?","answer":"Slightly smaller than the usual 1.5 ton unit but not that much of a difference","votes":"0","username":"bharat b.","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has 4 way swing mode","answer":"Yes...it has 4 way swing.","votes":"0","username":"Tech ji","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"This ac has own display","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Virendra Deo Verma","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model year shown in brand sticker 2021 but amazon shown 2022. Which one is correct","answer":"This is not true I have purchased 2022 model and same 2022 model I have received and written on my ac and box","votes":"0","username":"PANKAJ W.","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are we getting copper pipes and fitting material in box.","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Phani","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fae1cfba6a7877c09ec"},"product_asin":"B09NS6KFP1","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have low gas detection","answer":"It does not have low gas jndicator","votes":"0","username":"Nimit","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is interconnecting copper wire supplied with this AC when we buy online? as i see many people in recent review reported that Copper wire is missing.","answer":"Yes...10 ft wire is included.","votes":"0","username":"Kumar","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Copper pipe is included with this product?","answer":"Yes, it is included. If it doesn't come, register complaint at Amazon.","votes":"0","username":"Rohit kumar Bharti","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its cooling capacity","answer":"1 ton","votes":"0","username":"Rohit kumar Bharti","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"hot and cool option","answer":"Only cooling.","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep S.","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are installation charges included?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Virender Pal Singh","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"After buying this one Stabilizer is mandatory to fit","answer":"No. As per your area's electricity fluctuations.","votes":"0","username":"Virender Pal Singh","date":"2022-04-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf3fd11cfba6a7877c0e5b"},"product_asin":"B09NS6SS7T","QAs":[{"question":"Does this model has wifi?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"RANJAN","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c1e1921cfba6a7877e5f87"},"product_asin":"B09TJCL73K","QAs":[{"question":"Is it an inverter ac?","answer":"It's a Non-Inverter Air Conditioner","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62c9ccc91cfba6a787857712"},"product_asin":"B09RN3YRS6","QAs":[{"question":"Is bldc motor use on it?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it hot and cold ?","answer":"no, hot and cold model no kz24ykyf","votes":"0","username":"WONDERSHOPEE","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"}]}
